Word	POS Label	NER Label	Spacy POS Label	Spacy NER Label	Tweet
poutine	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1787 : i asked siri to remind me about my poutine in the office fridge but she misinterpreted and probably alerted the fbi . url222 …
friday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user912 : you know it 's friday when the port2port newsletter hits your inbox . sign up if you like fine wines too . url1265 …
@user444	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	mikel obi & his girl olga diyachenko spend holiday in spain with their kids … url1219 via @user444
@user1598	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	""" @user1598 : super junior ’s siwon transforms into ‘ captain choi ’ for “ poseidon ” url139 """
gospel	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	""" do n't move on from the gospel , move into the gospel ! "" todd friel"
gospel	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	""" do n't move on from the gospel , move into the gospel ! "" todd friel"
model	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	#follow us & #checkout the multi - talented spanglish / techno / pop singer / model @user779 aka lady boom boom url107
@user779	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	#follow us & #checkout the multi - talented spanglish / techno / pop singer / model @user779 aka lady boom boom url107
#fridaynightlights	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	#fridaynightlights viewing party at stick & stein in el segundo ! who 's with me ??
#harrypotter	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	#harrypotter marathon while i write my papers .
marathon	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	#harrypotter marathon while i write my papers .
#lebronshould	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	#lebronshould know his only championship is ' slam dunk ' . @user2004
#teamceltics	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	#teamceltics . lakers we coming for you .
#jordanheels	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	#jordanheels are very useful in a fight cause a hoodrat will put a jordan stamp n hole in ur dome lls
jordan	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	#jordanheels are very useful in a fight cause a hoodrat will put a jordan stamp n hole in ur dome lls
dj	PROPN	O	X	O	#np dj got us - falling in love ag - u$her ft. pitbull
@user676	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	#teamnevertoobusytotweet we are on it !!! @user676 url196
d	PROPN	O	X	O	3-0 !! phew !!! good no td !!! go job d !!! #birdgang
@user9	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user9 when have u ever said yes ... ?
@user15	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user15 what happened ?
@user48	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user48 ha !! damn auto spellcheck * rondo * lmbo
@user58	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user58 congrats !!! fredo noticed you !! please help me get noticed . :p
@user144	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user144 kmsl . leave anna out . of this . god ima have to hear about this all week huh
@user148	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user148 4 pages to be precise
@user155	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user155 that hurts !
@user156	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user156 i 'm allergic and they taste horrible
@user175	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user175 i ve been fine .. could be better lol [:
@user181	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user181 no , there are more extensive steps there . try them all , in order . ^ps
@user197	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user197 hehee , thankyou :d awh lmao :) xxx
@user200	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user200 ima get me a flip phone for real
@user205	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user205 i lost all my contacts , smh .
@user223	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user223 lmao i was waiting for u to say something after the barely pulled it out ....... they still weak as hell tho lol
@user233	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user233 u not callin me
@user257	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user257 i got some inking done on him this morning . not long now .
@user258	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user258 cuz i can n where u been biden at ?
@user305	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user305 thank you !!!!
@user308	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user308 i may have to get minecraft after watching videos of it
@user314	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user314 smh they had to book him fa something .. smh
@user315	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user315 if you 've got ta leave , make sure they never forget you . that 's what i do .
@user321	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user321 i miss fiko ..
@user342	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user342 otay
@user348	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user348 @user1252 2+4 = 6 i have 8 .
@user1252	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user348 @user1252 2+4 = 6 i have 8 .
@user372	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user372 ooooo you made my head spin with that one ! you are such a cheeky studmuffin !
@user407	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user407 lmfao !
@user416	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user416 he 1 shy of tie for most 3s in nba history and 2 shy of breaking it
@user440	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user440 ha . aha !!!!! you so nasty !!!!!!!.. but i like it lmao
@user473	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning #etp fam
@user948	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning #etp fam
@user1227	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning #etp fam
#etp	PROPN	O	X	B-ORG	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning #etp fam
@user481	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user481 most annoying song ever .
@user483	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user483 @user232 @user1743 niggas be lieing bout they do nt eat pussy but when it comes down to it they do it
@user232	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user483 @user232 @user1743 niggas be lieing bout they do nt eat pussy but when it comes down to it they do it
@user1743	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user483 @user232 @user1743 niggas be lieing bout they do nt eat pussy but when it comes down to it they do it
@user488	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user488 and uh next video shoot in the hood holla at a nigga ju heard ??
@user496	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user496 is having a giveaway ! url169 url169
@user499	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user499 lol where got ??
@user506	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user506 devoured it lol
@user516	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user516 follow me back yo !
@user534	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user534 wat channle
@user543	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user543 but it 's healthy cuz it has spinach !! ;)
@user554	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user554 hahahaha , maybe it s ment to be . (x
@user562	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user562 ok thank you !! :) i will check it out ♥
@user564	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user564 u eat sushi ?
@user566	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user566 17
@user574	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user574 lol u good just want to give credit where credit is due whensending to radio or tv cats needs their royalties nah mean !
@user575	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user575 yaaay ! ^.^
@user578	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user578 : it s lil bumbs around her lip and she swear it s her lipgloss #dumbniggathere < bumps * typo *
@user579	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user579 @user39 @user1719 yea i already had close to 160gig so i 'm probably at close to 190 gig now
@user39	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user579 @user39 @user1719 yea i already had close to 160gig so i 'm probably at close to 190 gig now
@user1719	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user579 @user39 @user1719 yea i already had close to 160gig so i 'm probably at close to 190 gig now
@user599	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user599 i wanted to tell him to sat his old ass down somewhere , doing the most ....
@user608	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user608 i know the feeling .
@user633	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user633 hey jream , where will the after party be at ?
@user641	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user641 yea from 7 - to 1 lol
@user649	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user649 get the new macbook air !!
@user657	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user657 no worries ... seems like a lot of people are busy
@user659	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user659 did u get that janette !? "" prefection rhymes with one direction "" not janette gonzalez . ~ lol"
@user681	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user681 i have them in my fridge right now , but they should be fine , i could freeze them if ya like .
@user706	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user706 i 'm off thursday . is that good for you ?
thursday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user706 i 'm off thursday . is that good for you ?
@user713	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user713 hey yh i 'm in bristol this saturday for my birthday , is der nefin goin on x
saturday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user713 hey yh i 'm in bristol this saturday for my birthday , is der nefin goin on x
@user716	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user716 they tryna close all the black hs 's in charlotte
hs	PROPN	O	X	O	@user716 they tryna close all the black hs 's in charlotte
@user721	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user721 i remember when you had like a thousand . you got the juice now .
@user726	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user726 is giving away 2 $ 250 grocery gift cards to associated foods . winner announced wed on 2news at 10 ! url84
wed	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	@user726 is giving away 2 $ 250 grocery gift cards to associated foods . winner announced wed on 2news at 10 ! url84
@user727	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user727 :/ it 's okay . i guess people are going again next week , do you think you 'll go ?
@user736	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user736 that how long my pubes are ? i 'm gon na go trim them too !
@user757	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user757 omg luke you need to watch remember me . i literally was balling . you 'd love it .
@user782	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user782 @user247 yes ! dm an email address to send the link to !
@user247	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user782 @user247 yes ! dm an email address to send the link to !
@user792	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user792 ... when will you come out to the field :)
@user797	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user797 cool , meet us at kieran 's if you can . court , too ? others ?
@user805	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user805 @user2113 glue our lips together with that black gunk !
@user2113	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user805 @user2113 glue our lips together with that black gunk !
@user834	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user834 lol , thanks . why you say that tho ? haha !!
@user839	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user839 western fries
@user857	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user857 lol it wasnt blood but thanks .
@user873	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user873 @user1561 miss y'all too just gon na leave me out the damn convo dicks lol
@user1561	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user873 @user1561 miss y'all too just gon na leave me out the damn convo dicks lol
@user902	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user902 weird cause your not doin either ..
@user909	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user909 that fallout vegas game looks neat
@user933	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user933 loolll i was lyin gem
@user939	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user939 if u want some funny & true quotes on your timeline then u should follow » @user91 « he 'll have u laughing all day !
@user91	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user939 if u want some funny & true quotes on your timeline then u should follow » @user91 « he 'll have u laughing all day !
@user942	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user942 @user2079 me three ! @user1323
@user2079	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user942 @user2079 me three ! @user1323
@user1323	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user942 @user2079 me three ! @user1323
@user955	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user955 looking good in the pic u put up
@user997	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user997 lmaooo iit was my mans .. iit was n't hurt at first but now i feel dat shiit
@user1016	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1016 she looks like it pacin' back & forth lol
@user1034	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1034 follow @user497 & win ca$h playing your favorite video games ! #gamersaloon
@user497	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1034 follow @user497 & win ca$h playing your favorite video games ! #gamersaloon
@user1038	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1038 lmao i 'm not a sheep who listens to it cos everyone else does , it s generally shit :(
@user1046	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1046 thnx
@user1064	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1064 knows what 's up . and what 's up is my dick .
@user1068	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1068 right ..
@user1082	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1082 when do you start your job ?
@user1101	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1101 lol no pork slime
@user1125	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1125 10th ... that random chicks nasty ass breath :-)
@user1127	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1127 lyod and wayne - you that was bigggg !
@user1161	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1161 idc we got rings we aint chumps
@user1178	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1178 ; awe you miss me ??
@user1183	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1183 #ynwa best wishes at this sad time
@user1210	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1210 it is google maps , but i do n't think it was a prank , it 's just the normal kind of thing that happens in germany
@user1213	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1213 what 's new ? lol
@user1306	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1306 omg u r from pa ? i am too (: where abouts ?
@user1309	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1309 in bham i & teamel_al will be in full effect 4 @user398 10/30/10 !
teamel_al	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	@user1309 in bham i & teamel_al will be in full effect 4 @user398 10/30/10 !
@user398	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1309 in bham i & teamel_al will be in full effect 4 @user398 10/30/10 !
@user1314	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1314 lets do the damn thing :]
@user1349	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1349 ok so we are cool i was n't sure smh i have people saying ridiculous stuff all day :( so sorry
@user1370	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1370 i think i cut like , 6 - 8 inches . it 's nice , but i miss my big ponytail !
@user1371	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1371 smfh that 's fucking crazy
@user1389	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1389 schl is ok so far .... will calll u soon ... still with my fone ... he is good ;-) hw r u ?
@user1398	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1398 yes . i 'm also gong to eastside 's pre-show rehearsal , and trying to go to yours as well . #teamdiddlehype #reppinhometeams
@user1419	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1419 hell yea
@user1448	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user1448 does n't change anything if it 's a "" best seller . "" ie @user695 and the wwe title . most businesses reinvest their profits into new things"
@user695	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user1448 does n't change anything if it 's a "" best seller . "" ie @user695 and the wwe title . most businesses reinvest their profits into new things"
title	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	"@user1448 does n't change anything if it 's a "" best seller . "" ie @user695 and the wwe title . most businesses reinvest their profits into new things"
@user1450	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1450 sup shirt off
@user1462	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1462 was guud shitty ass
@user1475	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1475 @user732 jesus are you two still at it ? lolx
@user732	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1475 @user732 jesus are you two still at it ? lolx
jesus	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user1475 @user732 jesus are you two still at it ? lolx
@user1496	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1496 yoy my cuzzin told me it came on @ 950
@user1502	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1502 @user1785 nah we thought of it a few days ago
@user1785	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1502 @user1785 nah we thought of it a few days ago
@user1514	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1514 yeh i have no idea but i cant wait xx
@user1529	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1529 you would have had 1,987,001 followers if you did <3 lol
@user1530	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1530 3 couplets , 1 refrain .
@user1531	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1531 lol i know ...
@user1542	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1542 lol !
@user1574	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1574 nice !
@user1585	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1585 lmfao that different
@user1601	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1601 thank you !
@user1647	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1647 follow @user1932 .. he has awesome quotes and your end up with wow .. :-) follow him if you like his tweets ..
@user1932	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1647 follow @user1932 .. he has awesome quotes and your end up with wow .. :-) follow him if you like his tweets ..
@user1671	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1671 oh ya i bet . should be lots of fun for you . lol :-)
@user1675	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1675 - lol i m jk ahah itss okayy ...
@user1683	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1683 hey :d please read this for me ! url191 i really wan na meet @user2082 in montreal ! <3
@user2082	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1683 hey :d please read this for me ! url191 i really wan na meet @user2082 in montreal ! <3
@user1720	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1720 kay !
@user1776	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1776 protester had 4 men tackle her down , cop just watched ? i knew chief of police in my city , corrupt as hell !! i 'm re- joining today
@user1780	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1780 : if a player wins his first match , then loses in the second round that 's a t-17 , technically . does that count as top - 25 ?
@user1848	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1848 naw naw ima have to lock up w his ass lol but she 's eating as usual 
@user1870	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1870 rt @user1915 : one day i hope you look back at what we had , and regret every single thing you did to let it end .
@user1877	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1877 cd : 90 % mp3 : 0 % vinyl : 10 %
@user1896	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1896 htb sneaker expo dec18th at 330 ritch in sf from 6 pm to 10 pm 18 & over . from l.a. 2 da bay !! please rt , thanks u coming ?
dec18th	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user1896 htb sneaker expo dec18th at 330 ritch in sf from 6 pm to 10 pm 18 & over . from l.a. 2 da bay !! please rt , thanks u coming ?
@user1909	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1909 how was paris !? xx
@user1958	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1958 you wo nt ?
@user1976	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1976 lol i know right
@user1978	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1978 lol thanks
@user1989	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1989 wow ! o.o
@user1993	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1993 nah u really do though . u r like on your 6 pic url81
@user1995	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1995 them breast is flirting with me boo smh
@user2005	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2005 hehe i 'm still on my summer vacation :) but if i do n't try get up earlier than now , i 'll definitely be late for school :'( #i4u
@user2026	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2026 i from in italy !!!!! and you ???
@user2030	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2030 okay ?
@user2059	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2059 brand new macbook with zero cost www.slop.in/qrvd
@user2060	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2060 the bbr aliases do n't add a space
@user2078	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2078 well me & her ..
@user2095	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2095 haha i know ... i said that school was gon na go down the hole after we left
@user2121	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2121 happy birthday !!!! i 'm so glad you were born ! you should have @user1624 take u out since he 's a texan again ... if u r town
@user1624	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2121 happy birthday !!!! i 'm so glad you were born ! you should have @user1624 take u out since he 's a texan again ... if u r town
@user2203	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2203 lol , we are one . and that was me this weekend especially . maybe put it off until you feel like ~ talking again ?
@user2217	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2217 @user999 @user1452 @user1162 and some others unfollowed me [ checked by url119 ]
@user999	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2217 @user999 @user1452 @user1162 and some others unfollowed me [ checked by url119 ]
@user1452	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2217 @user999 @user1452 @user1162 and some others unfollowed me [ checked by url119 ]
@user1162	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2217 @user999 @user1452 @user1162 and some others unfollowed me [ checked by url119 ]
@user2225	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2225 eh yeah i 'll be fine , just annoyed
@user2226	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2226 i love you more
@user2228	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2228 on my way ... lol
@user2229	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2229 of course she can come
@user2238	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2238 you suppose to say good'morning love ♥
@user2241	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2241 wow ! one of your best self portraits ever ! url211
@user2247	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2247 hey how is it going .. did u set it up ?
@user2252	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2252 can we go to tims please and tonkkss
tims	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	@user2252 can we go to tims please and tonkkss
tonkkss	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	@user2252 can we go to tims please and tonkkss
@user2256	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2256 i miss you too <3 i miss | california | but imma come see you as soon as i come back i #promise
california	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user2256 i miss you too <3 i miss | california | but imma come see you as soon as i come back i #promise
@user2260	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2260 * fingers crossed *
@user2301	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2301 home is where i 'd like to be right now ! my mom feeding me more than what i need . :) the best !
@user2302	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2302 lol looks like i hit the nail n the head with that one . ;-p
@user2310	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2310 good morning sexy one !
@user2371	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2371 wait a sec ... how late do you eat ?!? it 's like dinnertime here !
@user2390	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2390 why not ?!
@user2391	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2391 @user2508 actually sounds like it was too pit .
@user2508	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2391 @user2508 actually sounds like it was too pit .
@user2395	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2395 where did you ask ? we are very prompt with replies . if you want to dm your name or email we can check right now .
@user2411	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2411 heh . ca n't go wrong at minimum wage .
@user2422	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2422 there are more #creatures in donny 's room in today too bad you missed them :)
@user2425	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2425 lmao
@user2430	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2430 what 's that !
@user2455	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2455 hashy !!!!!! kiss my a ** lol
@user2458	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2458 well y da hell u did nt charge it ??
@user2465	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2465 i learned to knit so i could make wool soakers #fluffntreat
@user2471	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2471 stheriouthly .
@user2476	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2476 i 'm not too worried about the heat ... lebron never quits in important games versus the celtics ... oh wait
@user2493	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2493 i know but it 's long . it feels like math class .
@user2496	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2496 hiding from this tornado . how was that hibachi ? i got a taste for some
@user2497	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2497 honestly ? i have no idea . i just am ... all . the . time . :(
@user2502	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2502 glad #virgin is keeping you happy !
#virgin	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	@user2502 glad #virgin is keeping you happy !
@user2530	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2530 i like monkeys , but i still hate costco parking lots ..
@user2538	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2538 danilo gallinari
@user2553	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2553 the giants pitchers hair is as long as mine . ha !
@user2556	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2556 that good times episode was fucking hilarious
@user2595	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2595 i know but passing uni so i can go to america next year and stalk out corey , that 's a plan .
@user2599	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2599 true true . i 'm in love wit food nigga
@user2625	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2625 lol , naw , we good
@user2635	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2635 because i do n't have school on friday
friday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user2635 because i do n't have school on friday
@user2645	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2645 no you were right lol .. i do have to stop and i appreciate the input
flutes	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	ahh . flutes sound really bad with cheap mics . writing a song now , just need chords and i 'll be good . bye :d
@user1463	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	andrew - check out more tracks from the upcoming @user1463 albums : url95 & url100 :) .
h	PROPN	O	X	O	any haggis out there ? do n't say that ! what ? the ' h ' word . do n't say it ! all right ... are there any out there though ?
@user2427	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	awww @user2427 is going to bring a little girl on stage with her to sing ! :') she 's sooo nice ! :)
@user2304	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user187	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user2382	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user125	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user1779	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user813	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user2381	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
@user2380	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	ayeee do ya thing @user2304 @user187 @user2382 @user125 @user1779 @user813 @user2381 @user2380 shootn my movie
thursday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	bad loss for the bison men tonight at western illinois , against a team that got blown out by sdsu on thursday and was 1 - 5 in the summit .
bbm	PROPN	O	X	B-ORG	bbm yawn face * man that #napflow felt so refreshing .
#napflow	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	bbm yawn face * man that #napflow felt so refreshing .
@user227	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	bwaahaha that is classic . scoreboard ! ended your season . you got rolled by the team that lost to isu @user227 : @user168 husker fan
@user168	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	bwaahaha that is classic . scoreboard ! ended your season . you got rolled by the team that lost to isu @user227 : @user168 husker fan
suv	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	calgary 1980 pontiac trans am t tops $ 4,900.00 over 175 cars trucks and suv 's 90 day warrenty ... url175
@user2209	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	cartoons of the day url168 via @user2209
sunglasses	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	check this video out -- polaroid polarized sunglasses ( thailand ) url154 via @user2652
@user2652	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	check this video out -- polaroid polarized sunglasses ( thailand ) url154 via @user2652
@user2652	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	check this video out -- travie mccoy : billionaire ft. bruno mars ( audio ) url120 via @user2652
november	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	cold , raining , dark early . you 'd think it was november not august bank holiday weekend
august	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	cold , raining , dark early . you 'd think it was november not august bank holiday weekend
@user1035	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"david mitchell 's immersive reading room , the "" ultimate environment "" to enjoy thousand autumns : url75 /via @user1035"
early	PROPN	O	ADV	O	early bird special : conscious capitalism , new business model for 21st century in online masterclass - url60
bird	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	early bird special : conscious capitalism , new business model for 21st century in online masterclass - url60
special	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	early bird special : conscious capitalism , new business model for 21st century in online masterclass - url60
masterclass	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	early bird special : conscious capitalism , new business model for 21st century in online masterclass - url60
lady	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	freaky like my lady pyramid
pyramid	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	freaky like my lady pyramid
d	PROPN	O	X	O	first serious attack by philadelphia , but the timbers d got the ball out .
constantine	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	fucking bitches all the time i give em dick i m on dey mind i got angels demons constantine
@user2165	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	glad some network picked up #americasmostwanted . @user2165
#campuschat	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	got #college admissions questions ? ask them tonight during #campuschat i 'm looking forward to advice from @user1768 url38
@user1768	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	got #college admissions questions ? ask them tonight during #campuschat i 'm looking forward to advice from @user1768 url38
#jbspins	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	great review on #jbspins url77
uv	PROPN	O	VERB	O	haha . my producer said uv vodka is a bad situation waitin to happen , i said #fuuuuuuucccit
@user1769	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	hal sparks tonight @user1769 !! for tix url205 and enter the promo code juice !
valentine	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	happy valentine 's day ! ♥
@user1525	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	how ? rt @user595 : @user1525 lol dats so ugly
jasmine	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	hungryyyyy ( @ jasmine 26 ) url6
#teamceltics	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	i bet ! haha #teamceltics yesterday ! clowns ! rt @user167 : #teamheat at philly 2nite , let 's go !
#teamheat	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	i bet ! haha #teamceltics yesterday ! clowns ! rt @user167 : #teamheat at philly 2nite , let 's go !
#yelp	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	i checked in at dunkin donuts ( 1 congress st ) on #yelp url28
#celtics	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	i have always and forever will hate the #celtics
@user2450	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	i think i 'm a wait an hour or 2 & then tweet @user2450 ...
@user1490	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	i uploaded a @user1490 video url116 paris.flv
#bet	PROPN	O	VERB	O	idk what this movie on #bet is but i 've seen it before and it s hilarious !
@user1859	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	inspired after a yummy lunch with @user1859 . thanks !
giving	PROPN	O	VERB	O	is today thanks giving ? :l
jihad	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	islamic jihad militant killed near gaza border url36
january	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	january 16 , 2011 @user2408 will be in sm , cebu !!!!!
@user2408	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	january 16 , 2011 @user2408 will be in sm , cebu !!!!!
june	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	june 21 * sigh *
@user1322	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	lol .... i know that 's right ..... rt @user1322 @user773 and thank god 4 deliverance .... hiiiiya
@user773	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	lol .... i know that 's right ..... rt @user1322 @user773 and thank god 4 deliverance .... hiiiiya
@user359	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	making #travel a reality url160 @user359 #yakezie #lifestyle #budget #travelhacking
@user674	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	making moves ! are you ? url208 @user674 dude this is great find ! #tag
#lakers	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	man da #lakers have a fucking all - star squad fuck wit it !!
getto	PROPN	O	VERB	O	microwaved grilled cheese / the getto grilled cheese sandwhich / they 're made with real cheese #haiku #mooku
oem	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	motorola droid oem window mount – only for the first generation motorola droid : product descriptionthe motorola dr ... url32
window	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	motorola droid oem window mount – only for the first generation motorola droid : product descriptionthe motorola dr ... url32
mount	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	motorola droid oem window mount – only for the first generation motorola droid : product descriptionthe motorola dr ... url32
dr	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	motorola droid oem window mount – only for the first generation motorola droid : product descriptionthe motorola dr ... url32
monday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	next week - two morning zumba classes with me if you 're interested - monday nov 1st at 8:30 am and wednesday at ... url63
nov	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	next week - two morning zumba classes with me if you 're interested - monday nov 1st at 8:30 am and wednesday at ... url63
wednesday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	next week - two morning zumba classes with me if you 're interested - monday nov 1st at 8:30 am and wednesday at ... url63
gunrunner	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	"nick adamson 's online audition for gunrunner billy kane 's character "" the rat "" url65"
rat	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	"nick adamson 's online audition for gunrunner billy kane 's character "" the rat "" url65"
@user4	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	o_o lucky you .... llabd wutup doe ?! shine ! rt @user1078 : @user4 * yawns * still in the bed :)
loblaws	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	oh loblaws you kill me , 4 - 8
fitness	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	owning your craft in the fitness business - url151 #fitness bodybuilding #professionals #vancouver
business	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	owning your craft in the fitness business - url151 #fitness bodybuilding #professionals #vancouver
four	PROPN	O	NUM	B-MISC	ps : hearing the the early show cast get outraged by four loko was hilarious . made my morning and subsequent day . #parentsjustdontunderstand
loko	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	ps : hearing the the early show cast get outraged by four loko was hilarious . made my morning and subsequent day . #parentsjustdontunderstand
psp	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	psp .... phone ... ohmygoodlord technology why are you so great . it s also an ericsson which means @user1736 will just have to buy it . ;3
@user1736	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	psp .... phone ... ohmygoodlord technology why are you so great . it s also an ericsson which means @user1736 will just have to buy it . ;3
@user882	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user16 : fucking @user882 is louder than an group of barking dogs .
@user2652	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user411 laughing matter = me being serious . just watch . be encouraged !! url172 via @user2652
@user443	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user442 : exclusive picture of @user443 and jay 's mum sue ! url163
@user503	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user528 : @user503 read this !!! url133
@user557	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user592 : @user557 hang in there cousin love you
@user2554	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user696 : @user2554 thanks toby , someone posted a recap link here url26 , but i made it out injury free and feel g ...
@user1442	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user704 : @user1442 #libya breakthru ! we move urgently needed #food ( wheat , flour ) by truck convoy into western libya for 1st time ...
#libya	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user704 : @user1442 #libya breakthru ! we move urgently needed #food ( wheat , flour ) by truck convoy into western libya for 1st time ...
@user330	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user710 : @user330 aite bruh bruh i got you foue
@user334	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user799 : @user334 @user1374 @user1792 we just started this online petition . see how loved you all are ! :) url1 ...
@user1374	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user799 : @user334 @user1374 @user1792 we just started this online petition . see how loved you all are ! :) url1 ...
@user1792	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user799 : @user334 @user1374 @user1792 we just started this online petition . see how loved you all are ! :) url1 ...
@user831	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user846 : “ @user831 : #oomf is a liar , kaylee knows who i m talking about ” a lot of yur followers r liars ! lol
#oomf	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user846 : “ @user831 : #oomf is a liar , kaylee knows who i m talking about ” a lot of yur followers r liars ! lol
@user1967	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user920 : @user1967 @user940 lmao ! "" if you not down with birdman i ca n't fuck with you musically !!! "" < trueshit"
@user940	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user920 : @user1967 @user940 lmao ! "" if you not down with birdman i ca n't fuck with you musically !!! "" < trueshit"
trueshit	PROPN	O	ADJ	B-ORG	"rt @user920 : @user1967 @user940 lmao ! "" if you not down with birdman i ca n't fuck with you musically !!! "" < trueshit"
@user965	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user965 : rt @user1310 : @user965 this is my favorite screen shot from #rtm ;) ---> url198
#rtm	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user965 : rt @user1310 : @user965 this is my favorite screen shot from #rtm ;) ---> url198
@user2309	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user1008 : check out the hot new la artist @user2309 music . his new mixtape "" no turning back "" ===}} url74 ..."
@user2138	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1050 : @user2138 forget that ! i 'm ready for your u.s. tour in april and may of 2011 !!!! hell to the yes !!! #americaloveskylie
april	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1050 : @user2138 forget that ! i 'm ready for your u.s. tour in april and may of 2011 !!!! hell to the yes !!! #americaloveskylie
may	PROPN	O	AUX	O	rt @user1050 : @user2138 forget that ! i 'm ready for your u.s. tour in april and may of 2011 !!!! hell to the yes !!! #americaloveskylie
@user1197	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1069 where is punk ass , @user1197 tonite !!! < honestly who cares ?? :-p
tonite	PROPN	O	PART	O	rt @user1069 where is punk ass , @user1197 tonite !!! < honestly who cares ?? :-p
@user381	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1079 : always have your stuff when you need it with @user381 . 2gb account is free ! url148
prime	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1390 : berlusconi probed over cash - for - sex case : prime minister silvio berlusconi faces investigation in a prostitution ... htt ...
minister	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1390 : berlusconi probed over cash - for - sex case : prime minister silvio berlusconi faces investigation in a prostitution ... htt ...
cato	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1487 : i blow supplies up in the air sometimes saying ayoo take that cato
@user664	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1511 : do n't nonsense ley ! we brother sister ! :d @user664 i thought you love @user1478 ma !
@user1478	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1511 : do n't nonsense ley ! we brother sister ! :d @user664 i thought you love @user1478 ma !
@user2024	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1655 : . #walesaid dt @user2024 should go downtown ! lol !!.. #jammy --> lmao !! man bianca !!!
#jammy	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user1655 : . #walesaid dt @user2024 should go downtown ! lol !!.. #jammy --> lmao !! man bianca !!!
#mnd	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1767 : check out url42 . freezing my nads in the snow , naked for #mnd charity . £ 4.5 k raised so far . please rt ! thx .
charity	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1767 : check out url42 . freezing my nads in the snow , naked for #mnd charity . £ 4.5 k raised so far . please rt ! thx .
@user2065	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1803 : @user2065 oh , hey thanks jerk !
@user715	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1908 : i saw @user715 : never say never and here 's what i thought : url118 viva el biebs !!
@user1917	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1917 : rt @user2129 : #random ii love how this nigga @user1917 kome in with the singing on #hawthornenigga #noelton - ...
#hawthornenigga	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	rt @user1917 : rt @user2129 : #random ii love how this nigga @user1917 kome in with the singing on #hawthornenigga #noelton - ...
#noelton	PROPN	O	DET	B-ORG	rt @user1917 : rt @user2129 : #random ii love how this nigga @user1917 kome in with the singing on #hawthornenigga #noelton - ...
@user610	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1962 : shout - out to @user610 definition of lil webbies i-n-d-e-p-e-n-d-e-n-t --> do you know what means man ??? « ayyye !
lil	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1962 : shout - out to @user610 definition of lil webbies i-n-d-e-p-e-n-d-e-n-t --> do you know what means man ??? « ayyye !
webbies	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1962 : shout - out to @user610 definition of lil webbies i-n-d-e-p-e-n-d-e-n-t --> do you know what means man ??? « ayyye !
@user74	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1987 : @user74 got them black girl groupies though
@user623	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2087 : @user623 do nt really know where i would be without you and demi <3 i luv youuuu
@user787	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2105 : @user787 this park is the cutest thing ever omg url104
@user2327	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2373 : hello , i 'm at @user2327 's home with @user404 @user2349 @user2219 and @user2498 :)
@user404	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2373 : hello , i 'm at @user2327 's home with @user404 @user2349 @user2219 and @user2498 :)
@user2349	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2373 : hello , i 'm at @user2327 's home with @user404 @user2349 @user2219 and @user2498 :)
@user2219	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2373 : hello , i 'm at @user2327 's home with @user404 @user2349 @user2219 and @user2498 :)
@user2498	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2373 : hello , i 'm at @user2327 's home with @user404 @user2349 @user2219 and @user2498 :)
@user1152	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2405 « @user1152 @user401 cuffin in the avi , gim me $ 20 »
@user401	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2405 « @user1152 @user401 cuffin in the avi , gim me $ 20 »
@user1426	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2514 : i got to say ' peace up , a - town down ' in atlanta then @user1426 came out and sang ' yeah ! ' with me . i 'm thinking ...
@user2317	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2563 : there is no new media : it ’s all new consumption by @user2317 url29 #newspaper #media
@user1295	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rain rain go away <-- our song is on @user1295 i kid you not 107.5
id	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	ruling strikes down part of arizona voter id law - yahoo! news url70
live	PROPN	O	VERB	O	showoffradio live !!!
@user776	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	sad ! you called me a liar when i was searous . you know you were my bottom bish ! rt @user984 : @user776 ahahha liar ! how are u ?
@user2102	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	someone is n't replying back ! @user2102
@user1143	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	stupid kilkenny did n't get to meet @user1143 :/
@user244	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	tagged : @user244 @user2193 - url117
@user2193	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	tagged : @user244 @user2193 - url117
ex	PROPN	O	X	O	the modern vacation : with ex ’s and new partners url150
@user2350	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the onion weighs in on the wisconsin senate race url99 via @user2350
boots	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	ty beanie babies - set of 2 beanies ( dora & boots ) : ty beanie babies set of 2- dora the explorer and boots url144
boots	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	ty beanie babies - set of 2 beanies ( dora & boots ) : ty beanie babies set of 2- dora the explorer and boots url144
wednesday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	wednesday 27th october 2010 . 》 have a nice day :)
october	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	wednesday 27th october 2010 . 》 have a nice day :)
#jeopardy	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	weird , #jeopardy is alluding to the charlie the unicorn video in their clue titles ! shun the non-believer !
pimpin	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-PER	whaddup pimpin ken . ha !
@user135	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	where 's the video @user135 & @user2519 took of me ?? exactly ! lmao
@user2519	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	where 's the video @user135 & @user2519 took of me ?? exactly ! lmao
#snowto	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	where 's this #snowto at ? let 's see what you 've got #toronto
nnw	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	wind 2.2 mph nnw . barometer 1019.0 mb , rising . temperature 15.5 °c . rain today 0.0 mm . humidity 59 %
@user1575	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	yeeeeeees lakers !!! rt @user735 : @user1575 the laker girls danced to fye at halftime !!
xmas	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	[ post ] spammy ’s 12 days of xmas : day 2 – burning the tool log url129
@user2138	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	check out kylie minogue north american tour 2011 url101 via @user2138
@user1707	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	hello @user1707 , i miss you , i love you ! ♥ #4
@user2615	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	url43 making it easy to put up a @user2615 , @user2070 in the cloud #aws
@user2070	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	url43 making it easy to put up a @user2615 , @user2070 in the cloud #aws
@user2082	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	url207 @user2082 look what i made ?
@user1881	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	i heart @user1881 's true music that inspires me to intake my beauty , roots , and willingness to take on anything .
@user375	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	if @user375 do nt make some hoodies soon ... imma beat em !
#miamiheat	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	it s the sixers rt @user639 #miamiheat gettin it 2gether now ... #ilike
@user2649	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	nowfollowing @user2649 lem me give him a quick s\o !!! ladies follow him he 's #teamfollowback hey chris !!!
wessss	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	wessss keep metal hjahah \m/ rt @user47 : metal
@user741	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"« @user741 #kayoq & a ladies what if u tell a guy "" i love you "" and he says "" oh ok "" ....... then what ? » then he do n't love you lol"
#kayoq	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	"« @user741 #kayoq & a ladies what if u tell a guy "" i love you "" and he says "" oh ok "" ....... then what ? » then he do n't love you lol"
@user601	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	“ @user601 blueroom may 19th fems free and drink free til 11:30 $ 5 all night behind winn dixie on pinehills road leggooo ”
may	PROPN	O	AUX	O	“ @user601 blueroom may 19th fems free and drink free til 11:30 $ 5 all night behind winn dixie on pinehills road leggooo ”
fems	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	“ @user601 blueroom may 19th fems free and drink free til 11:30 $ 5 all night behind winn dixie on pinehills road leggooo ”
@user1305	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	“ @user1305 : i just voted for ian somerhalder #tvdramaactor #peopleschoice . retweet to vote url130 via @user2342 ”
@user2342	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	“ @user1305 : i just voted for ian somerhalder #tvdramaactor #peopleschoice . retweet to vote url130 via @user2342 ”
@user698	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2212 : @user698 i 'll literally be there at 7:07 . :d
dawn	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1504 : it is always darkest before the dawn ! we are passing through the darkest times in pak history , fajr can not be far .. ht …
g310	PROPN	O	SYM	B-MISC	g310 . not bad !! ( pic via fb ) url1021
fb	PROPN	O	INTJ	O	g310 . not bad !! ( pic via fb ) url1021
@user2343	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2343 she should be killed in the same way .
@user1170	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1170 investigate for you . i hope this helps . 3/3 ^ gareth url735
svt	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1855 : svt when people keep voting for sweden url1528
@user2613	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2613 a followback , please ? 🐙
grill	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	free char - broil grill ( hilliard ) url1473
@user2481	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2481 maybe 😂
@user371	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user313 : #newmusic #rapvideos bounce by @user371 ft @user241 #mtvblog ... url388
@user241	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user313 : #newmusic #rapvideos bounce by @user371 ft @user241 #mtvblog ... url388
@user963	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the @user963 draft is thursday makes me want to play @user388 anyone want to get down ?? #youdontwantitwithme !
thursday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	the @user963 draft is thursday makes me want to play @user388 anyone want to get down ?? #youdontwantitwithme !
@user388	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the @user963 draft is thursday makes me want to play @user388 anyone want to get down ?? #youdontwantitwithme !
#teenchoice	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	my #teenchoice for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016
#choicemusicgroup	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	my #teenchoice for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016
@user21	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	my #teenchoice for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016
@user2196	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user2196 well next time i need a spoon , i will define the term "" illegal """
@user693	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user693 alright bro
@user1934	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	retweeted globalpublishing ( @user1934 ) : atmosphere permits light and heat to reach earth at levels ... url534
@user1860	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user1860 giving us insights on global governance at @user1254 "" we want more than we need "" url626"
@user1254	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user1860 giving us insights on global governance at @user1254 "" we want more than we need "" url626"
#24audiolaunch	PROPN	O	NUM	B-MISC	rt @user2020 : to all suriya fans coming to #24audiolaunch on monday - no photos or videos allowed inside the venue .
monday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2020 : to all suriya fans coming to #24audiolaunch on monday - no photos or videos allowed inside the venue .
friday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	friday night making our sound system smile -> url1484 url1246
@user2659	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2659 you are just a little boy from bradford and now you are smashing it . so fucking proud
mge	PROPN	O	VERB	B-ORG	solo queue ( ~ mge ) is close to being unplayable . url640 @user476 #csgo
@user476	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	solo queue ( ~ mge ) is close to being unplayable . url640 @user476 #csgo
#soundcloud	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	listen to 15 - it s like that featuring kast ki bohiti ( produced by lilzhp ) by king problem #np on #soundcloud url1630
#periscope	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	live on #periscope : thursday 's fundraising tip : stay in touch with supporters ! #fundraiser #schools #church #succes … url1151
thursday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	live on #periscope : thursday 's fundraising tip : stay in touch with supporters ! #fundraiser #schools #church #succes … url1151
motocross	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	moto gp 46 racing polo t-shirt sport men's motorcycle bike yamaha motocross url739 url527
ft	PROPN	O	INTJ	O	when ya friend fake tired so she do n't have to answer your ft 🙃 @user49
@user49	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	when ya friend fake tired so she do n't have to answer your ft 🙃 @user49
#mpoints	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	i 'm earning #mpoints with #askdaball ! url1271 #app
#askdaball	PROPN	O	VERB	B-ORG	i 'm earning #mpoints with #askdaball ! url1271 #app
directioners	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	power of directioners go directioners go directioners will rise #bestfanarmy #directioners #iheartawards walking in the wind
directioners	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	power of directioners go directioners go directioners will rise #bestfanarmy #directioners #iheartawards walking in the wind
directioners	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	power of directioners go directioners go directioners will rise #bestfanarmy #directioners #iheartawards walking in the wind
roxas	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	roxas rising url1024
@user811	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user811 hi , linda ! it seems so based on statements hrc has made ... bs and hrc are meeting tomorrow . we shall see ...
kumamon	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	#ystl minyoonjgi hi cutie how was your day ? if you had a bad day look at this handsome photo of me . fr kumamon url278
h	PROPN	O	X	O	h ! @user548 ♡ “ the universe is in your bones , the stars in your soul … ” do you mind following me ? thank you for everything x 🌟 – 730,777
@user548	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	h ! @user548 ♡ “ the universe is in your bones , the stars in your soul … ” do you mind following me ? thank you for everything x 🌟 – 730,777
@user750	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user750 congratulations .
cavsin6	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458
@user225	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458
@user1211	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458
@user1348	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458
@user458	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458
@user2259	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2259 your answer is limits ...
@user2540	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2540 hey the normal thing was from me
wic	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2607 : reset epson waste ink counter overflow by wic and reset key url469 #wic #resetkey #epson #printer
@user353	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user353 i swear 💯
@user1775	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	haiti earthquake 2011 . hillary 's brother got the gold mine . haiti got the shaft . url1453 @user1775 #dncphl #dncconvention
@user992	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1 : @user992 when you are constantly interrupted by @user513 tonight , as you will be , please ask him why he is so fear …
@user513	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1 : @user992 when you are constantly interrupted by @user513 tonight , as you will be , please ask him why he is so fear …
@user423	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2486 : @user423 multimedia earned money url1114
@user1477	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user751 : wow the place is packed ! good luck @user1477 let your star shine it s brightest ! #adatewithxian url1267
@user2659	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2659 follow me ×5129
@user993	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user847 : one final team check ahead of kick - off . @user993 in the tweet seat for you at #cityvreal . how 're we all feeling ?! url224 …
#cityvreal	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user847 : one final team check ahead of kick - off . @user993 in the tweet seat for you at #cityvreal . how 're we all feeling ?! url224 …
qb	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	cam : why carolina panthers ' new qb is the worst nfl draft pick ever | bleacher report ( via url1581 ) url1302
@user1027	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1027 @user406 i do n't like eminem but he said the right words . 2 pac changed rap music in much ways . salute . #realnigga 👑👌
@user406	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1027 @user406 i do n't like eminem but he said the right words . 2 pac changed rap music in much ways . salute . #realnigga 👑👌
@user1923	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1923 did n't eat enough did i 🙄
@user11	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user11 free 4th of july concert at operanightclub in atl 🎉 url1406 #savagemode rt x14
july	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user11 free 4th of july concert at operanightclub in atl 🎉 url1406 #savagemode rt x14
@user705	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user705 @user883 @user1437 the band from the carl 's jr commercial ?
@user883	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user705 @user883 @user1437 the band from the carl 's jr commercial ?
@user1437	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user705 @user883 @user1437 the band from the carl 's jr commercial ?
@user1006	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user563 : listen : @user1006 feat. elan noelle – i like the way url1596
@user2066	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	oh yeah ! spanked em ! way to go @user2066 #nascar 🏁 #ford
@user2291	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2291 : up first this morning for @user2291 is the history of time travel @user1058 @user582 #pff2016 #ihsff url221 …
@user2253	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user420	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user335	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user2377	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user1375	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user821	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
june	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	@user2253 @user420 @user335 @user2377 @user1375 @user821 , dude , relax . trump will dominate in california come june 7th .
@user1829	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1829 literally us 20 minutes ago url269
#littlemix	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1724 : who are the biggest girl band on the planet right now ? #littlemix or @user450
@user450	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1724 : who are the biggest girl band on the planet right now ? #littlemix or @user450
may	PROPN	O	AUX	O	may 2015 was everything 😪
#yakima	PROPN	O	X	B-MISC	join the country financial team ! see our latest #sales #job opening here : url496 #yakima , wa url333
bright	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	rt @user2330 : save the best for you shine bright glen
@user1577	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1577 @user1678 @user1632 @user85 dashiki shirt to who said that it looked awesome
@user1678	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1577 @user1678 @user1632 @user85 dashiki shirt to who said that it looked awesome
@user1632	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1577 @user1678 @user1632 @user85 dashiki shirt to who said that it looked awesome
@user85	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1577 @user1678 @user1632 @user85 dashiki shirt to who said that it looked awesome
dashiki	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	@user1577 @user1678 @user1632 @user85 dashiki shirt to who said that it looked awesome
@user29	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user29 @user2442 @user2265 i 'm grateful for this all happening bc there is no ( cont ) url338
@user2442	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user29 @user2442 @user2265 i 'm grateful for this all happening bc there is no ( cont ) url338
@user2265	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user29 @user2442 @user2265 i 'm grateful for this all happening bc there is no ( cont ) url338
@user1563	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1563 1 out of 10
#espys	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	"rt @user1292 : the #espys open with a powerful black lives matter tribute : "" we all have to do better "" url497 url621 …"
mrs	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1346 : when your mate who 's mrs rarely lets him out makes it to the pub url1013
@user50	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user50 @user103 4/4 hai yogendra yadav confirmed in public that you were aware of tomar 's farzi degree well in advance
@user103	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user50 @user103 4/4 hai yogendra yadav confirmed in public that you were aware of tomar 's farzi degree well in advance
dojo	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	dojo news : ahead of all - american top team title fight , take a tour of the team ’s new florida headquarters url1240
news	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	dojo news : ahead of all - american top team title fight , take a tour of the team ’s new florida headquarters url1240
@user1789	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1789 😅😂 ima just shut up 🙂☝🏽️
cnblue	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user966 : 20160319 cnblue #cometogetherinchongqing url767 url1452
@user1278	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1278 @user867 @user1643 my eyes say it s him , haha .. but my eyes can be wrong ..
@user867	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1278 @user867 @user1643 my eyes say it s him , haha .. but my eyes can be wrong ..
@user1643	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1278 @user867 @user1643 my eyes say it s him , haha .. but my eyes can be wrong ..
zig	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user1760 : crocodiles are fast on their feet , but can not turn very well . if one is chasing you , run in zig zag lines .
zag	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user1760 : crocodiles are fast on their feet , but can not turn very well . if one is chasing you , run in zig zag lines .
@user720	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user720 dylan and chris wo nt be there will they ?
july	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	"rt @user2443 : take advantage of our july 4th sales event ! use the code "" july4 "" for 15 % off your order ! 🇺🇸 url465 💪🏼 url218 …"
#gbv	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1411 : women are more likely to experience physical violence committed by their spouse than men . speak up against #gbv . url222 …
@user1479	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	#ff @user1479 the national campaign dedicated 2 tackling youth unemployment . home of the youth friendly badge & youth employment e-magazine
#studentexperience	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	"rt @user2154 : "" the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today "" #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …"
@user2155	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user2154 : "" the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today "" #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …"
#uniexperience	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	"rt @user2154 : "" the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today "" #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …"
@user1622	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1622 @user218 will you please help pass the message about my aunties dying wish on @user1885 it would mean so much to me and her 💖
@user218	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1622 @user218 will you please help pass the message about my aunties dying wish on @user1885 it would mean so much to me and her 💖
@user1885	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1622 @user218 will you please help pass the message about my aunties dying wish on @user1885 it would mean so much to me and her 💖
guilty	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	rt @user1456 : dizzy in guilty gear #evo2016 url401
gear	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1456 : dizzy in guilty gear #evo2016 url401
@user1483	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1017 : only 26 away from 500 ! awesome growth over the last month . thank you everyone . can we get to 500 ? @user1483 @user437 #sma …
@user437	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1017 : only 26 away from 500 ! awesome growth over the last month . thank you everyone . can we get to 500 ? @user1483 @user437 #sma …
#amazon	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	the easiest way to make money with #amazon #affiliate url1558 #blogging #webmaster google 's parent company alphabet is …
#affiliate	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	the easiest way to make money with #amazon #affiliate url1558 #blogging #webmaster google 's parent company alphabet is …
@user126	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user126 he listened
@user1828	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user170 : "" they "" do n't want you to be concerned about climate change , but @user1828 & i want you to be . major 🔑 / major 🔬 url1175 …"
@user189	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user189 @user1237 oh cry me a river will you 🙄
@user1237	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user189 @user1237 oh cry me a river will you 🙄
@user2564	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1473 : not included in that was the growing , scary abuse , & racial attacks occurring on & offline post brexit @user2564 h …
#westworld	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1677 : our genius producer / writers / showrunners answer a few things about #westworld url1555
uk	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	i totally agree ban islam uk url512
@user397	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user397 we love you ekpe please !!
ekpe	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	@user397 we love you ekpe please !!
march	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user576 : whoo ! on march 16th i 'll be having a charity stream on twitch to benefit @user1059 !! mark your calendars ! url221 …
@user1059	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user576 : whoo ! on march 16th i 'll be having a charity stream on twitch to benefit @user1059 !! mark your calendars ! url221 …
@user1503	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1503 most of them think they are little experts especially if u r at that shea one
iu	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user2619 : rt iuqties : do n't forget that ftisland 's jaejin also is a fan of iu ! 😂 url1124
@user2235	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2235 @user192 @user191 @user55 thanks for gant btw hope 2 months of kelly johnson was worth it last year
@user192	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2235 @user192 @user191 @user55 thanks for gant btw hope 2 months of kelly johnson was worth it last year
@user191	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2235 @user192 @user191 @user55 thanks for gant btw hope 2 months of kelly johnson was worth it last year
@user55	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2235 @user192 @user191 @user55 thanks for gant btw hope 2 months of kelly johnson was worth it last year
@user1795	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1795 absolutely
@user1985	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1985 @user1943 why is the ups man lying dead on your living room floor ?
@user1943	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1985 @user1943 why is the ups man lying dead on your living room floor ?
#9thehabibs	PROPN	O	NUM	B-MISC	watching #9thehabibs is like hanging out with my in - laws . yella habibi ! 😂
yella	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	watching #9thehabibs is like hanging out with my in - laws . yella habibi ! 😂
habibi	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	watching #9thehabibs is like hanging out with my in - laws . yella habibi ! 😂
@user104	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user982 : this for you @user104 url1130
@user986	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	new lara vapnyer in @user986 this week ! :d this will be my special treat after i am finished teaching for the day . hearts
@user728	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user728 so to hai
@user400	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user100 : congratulations to @user400 on topping our march goal of the month poll ! watch it here : url1551 url225 …
march	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user100 : congratulations to @user400 on topping our march goal of the month poll ! watch it here : url1551 url225 …
po	PROPN	O	INTJ	O	rt @user2298 : uhm funny po ako 😹 thank you po ! #stbratsexhibit url655
ako	PROPN	O	DET	B-ORG	rt @user2298 : uhm funny po ako 😹 thank you po ! #stbratsexhibit url655
po	PROPN	O	INTJ	O	rt @user2298 : uhm funny po ako 😹 thank you po ! #stbratsexhibit url655
@user1611	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1611 strangers not allowed sorry
@user2426	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	could n't tweet on way back down bc i was carrying jug ... @user2426 url467
@user549	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"rt @user40 : wenger : "" we are a bit short on goal scored . we will try to certainly strengthen in that department . "" [ @user549 ] htt …"
keen	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	url824 retweeted i 'm in the arndale centre i have 8 hours to wait for the signing talk about keen url690
@user2187	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2187 turn my notifications off so you do n't see my 200 mispellings out of 200 tweets
@user2134	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2134 follow back ... i need to dm you
@user1824	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	dear @user1824 's girlfriend . you won the guy we all dreamed of having . so please . do us a favor . hold him and never let him go .
@user1559	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1559 i have
#teenchoice	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	ix my #teenchoice nominee for #socialmediaqueen #choicefemalehottie #choiceinstagrammer is britney spears
#socialmediaqueen	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	ix my #teenchoice nominee for #socialmediaqueen #choicefemalehottie #choiceinstagrammer is britney spears
#choicefemalehottie	PROPN	O	ADJ	B-ORG	ix my #teenchoice nominee for #socialmediaqueen #choicefemalehottie #choiceinstagrammer is britney spears
#choiceinstagrammer	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-PER	ix my #teenchoice nominee for #socialmediaqueen #choicefemalehottie #choiceinstagrammer is britney spears
@user913	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user637 : underground clinics in turkey treating syria 's wounded jihadist terrorists to fight on url539 via @user913 …
@user1825	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1825 @user2546 i was trying to be as nice as i could without blowing up or cussing
@user2546	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1825 @user2546 i was trying to be as nice as i could without blowing up or cussing
@user2479	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user634 : hugely proud to have won a @user2479 innovation excellence award for our #graphicmedicine #comics ! url1216 …
asif	PROPN	O	ADP	B-ORG	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
siddiqui	PROPN	O	X	B-ORG	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
daily	PROPN	O	ADV	B-MISC	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
@user2204	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
@user1267	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
@user2577	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	the latest the asif siddiqui daily ! url1500 thanks to @user2204 @user1267 @user2577 #food #foodie
friday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user777 : friday night at #sdcc2016 with sis , @user1679 covered in magic ! #onceuponatime #evilregalsdcc ❤️🦄💚 url1178
#sdcc2016	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user777 : friday night at #sdcc2016 with sis , @user1679 covered in magic ! #onceuponatime #evilregalsdcc ❤️🦄💚 url1178
@user1679	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user777 : friday night at #sdcc2016 with sis , @user1679 covered in magic ! #onceuponatime #evilregalsdcc ❤️🦄💚 url1178
marathon	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	""" in marathon filibuster , democrats call for gun limits "" by jonah engel bromwich via nyt the new york times url916"
filibuster	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	""" in marathon filibuster , democrats call for gun limits "" by jonah engel bromwich via nyt the new york times url916"
@user598	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user598 probably a fake stomach
#hyderabad	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user559 : join us in #hyderabad for hands - on experience with #smartmapp technology ! #igniteyourmapp url747 htt …
#smartmapp	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	rt @user559 : join us in #hyderabad for hands - on experience with #smartmapp technology ! #igniteyourmapp url747 htt …
@user2144	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2144 : @user2144 like pay attention to me ugh
@user2162	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2097 : @user2162 stop comparing fergie to iggy because fergie is so talented & ti writes iggys music ( when she had hits ) double …
@user1813	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1813 how has your day been ? i hope it 's been amazing . 😊
june	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1990 : oneplus 3 to come to india 15th june will start at rs. 23999 url951 #oneplus #india #oneplus3
rs.	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1990 : oneplus 3 to come to india 15th june will start at rs. 23999 url951 #oneplus #india #oneplus3
#gameofthrones	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user2549 : rt this tweet to win tickets to an exclusive london #gameofthrones s5 screening on march 14 ! uk only - closes 3/3 ! url224 …
s5	PROPN	O	PART	B-MISC	rt @user2549 : rt this tweet to win tickets to an exclusive london #gameofthrones s5 screening on march 14 ! uk only - closes 3/3 ! url224 …
march	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2549 : rt this tweet to win tickets to an exclusive london #gameofthrones s5 screening on march 14 ! uk only - closes 3/3 ! url224 …
@user638	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user638 hey baby thanks for being the best . so glad you 're all mine 😘😘😘💘
pc	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user511 : asus gaming pc giveaway follow me & @user490 turn on mobile notifications retweet this tweet url253 …
@user2647	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2647 hit the weights 🐱
@user1242	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1242 @user1620 @user2170 @user2061 thanks lovely brother !
@user1620	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1242 @user1620 @user2170 @user2061 thanks lovely brother !
@user2170	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1242 @user1620 @user2170 @user2061 thanks lovely brother !
@user2061	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1242 @user1620 @user2170 @user2061 thanks lovely brother !
@user121	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	istanbul airport attack : 23 turks , at least 10 foreign nationals killed , officials say , as ... url880 via @user121
@user1142	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1142 yeah . ignored need basically .
#dollyparton	PROPN	O	ADV	B-ORG	#dollyparton announces first tour in over 25 years #dollyparton ... #dollyparton url766
@user2264	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2264 lmfaooooo i wish i could rt that . you are honest af
#designshanghai	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user361 : deeply saddened by the news of zaha hadid 's passing , we remember her amazing work at #designshanghai 2016 . url224 …
@user2227	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	i saw this early & thought it was pretty fun to watch ! @user2227 was great ! are you going to see it ? 🎬🎥 url370
rugby	PROPN	O	VERB	O	what a tough half of rugby league ! impressed with our uncompromising defence , it 's a big effort to nil leeds in a half ! #wire
league	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	what a tough half of rugby league ! impressed with our uncompromising defence , it 's a big effort to nil leeds in a half ! #wire
@user103	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user103 intension makes the difference
#caveman	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user60 : it 's a strong look ! the #caveman gym #kitbag used by @user1489 bowler @user202 #teamaffinity #gymferret 👊💪 url217 …
@user1489	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user60 : it 's a strong look ! the #caveman gym #kitbag used by @user1489 bowler @user202 #teamaffinity #gymferret 👊💪 url217 …
@user202	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user60 : it 's a strong look ! the #caveman gym #kitbag used by @user1489 bowler @user202 #teamaffinity #gymferret 👊💪 url217 …
@user560	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user865 : @user560 that was good .. he was a little bit better today and enjoyed sun and garden :-)) have a good nite .. see ye
@user1977	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1977 @user2111 follow me pls
@user2111	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1977 @user2111 follow me pls
@user390	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user390 a1 ) stutterheim asked attendees to dress in white as a tribute to his brother miles #edmlispecial #sensationindia #hyderabad
k-pop	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	"my friend : "" do you love k-pop ? you ’re not a korean . ” /// me : “ why ? do we need to be italian to love pizza ? ”"
@user2339	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	congrats @user2339 2nd best sommelière in the world and 4th among all contendants at #bestworldsommarg2016 . #vamospaz felicidades !!!
sommelière	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	congrats @user2339 2nd best sommelière in the world and 4th among all contendants at #bestworldsommarg2016 . #vamospaz felicidades !!!
#bestworldsommarg2016	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	congrats @user2339 2nd best sommelière in the world and 4th among all contendants at #bestworldsommarg2016 . #vamospaz felicidades !!!
@user1748	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1748 @user299 aye we getting inked up over here in the chi ! talking about sleeves and shit ! lol
@user299	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1748 @user299 aye we getting inked up over here in the chi ! talking about sleeves and shit ! lol
@user1440	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	want a chance to win some prizes from @user1440 ? just head over to @user2630 and enter ! url856
@user2630	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	want a chance to win some prizes from @user1440 ? just head over to @user2630 and enter ! url856
#xboxone	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1103 : who wants to win a #xboxone ? simply retweet to everyone & follow us to enter contest url947 url222 …
friday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	i 'm gon na kms just got txt saying we have practice like wth it 's friday i got plans
@user2424	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2424 their *****
@user1240	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1466 : // guys shoutout to @user1240 go rp with him he needs more sls !
rp	PROPN	O	INTJ	O	rt @user1466 : // guys shoutout to @user1240 go rp with him he needs more sls !
sls	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1466 : // guys shoutout to @user1240 go rp with him he needs more sls !
@user1555	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	"@user1555 lmaoooo my whole history "" 😂 """
xmas	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	#golfing #golfnews 1999 new in box mr christmas animated musical golfing santa 15 xmas ... url1119 url656
@user68	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1089 : more : some of hospitalized got critical trauma stab wounds url1307 pic by @user68 #sacramento url219 …
#contestalert	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1270 : #contestalert show us some love ! gear up for #sultantraileronsony at 7 pm because it 's sultan trailer day !
#sultantraileronsony	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	rt @user1270 : #contestalert show us some love ! gear up for #sultantraileronsony at 7 pm because it 's sultan trailer day !
@user1060	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	end of 1st : condors up 2 - 1 with goals from @user1060 & @user1214 . #condorstown
@user1214	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	end of 1st : condors up 2 - 1 with goals from @user1060 & @user1214 . #condorstown
#educatorsplaybook	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1048 : #educatorsplaybook : @user379 offers advice for high school athletes choosing colleges url572 url222 …
@user379	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1048 : #educatorsplaybook : @user379 offers advice for high school athletes choosing colleges url572 url222 …
@user523	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user523 okay i see you getting a little color in yo skin
@user2279	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2279 lolol .. i cant remember which site but it was postes while bap was in north america
@user2472	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2472 please submit a request and tweet back your ticket so we can help to resolve this issue : url1328 thanks ! * mh
july	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user172 : today is july 396th and still no frank ocean album
valentine	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	📷 erzascrlt : happy valentine ’s day from aqours 💖 url785
@user1581	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …
carvan	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-PER	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …
vl	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …
caravan	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …
#200daysmsg2	PROPN	O	NUM	B-MISC	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …
@user1086	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2520 : can not wait to see @user1086 's latest masterpieces at the btc premiere ! ✨ url1014
@user2582	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	i just earned the ' newbie ' badge on @user2582 ! url716
@user888	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1914 : . @user888 is looking for some #genstemgirls to help make the world a better place . sounds like a job for girl scouts ! url218 …
#genstemgirls	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1914 : . @user888 is looking for some #genstemgirls to help make the world a better place . sounds like a job for girl scouts ! url218 …
nike	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	new nike sb : £ 15.00 ( 0 bids ) end date : wednesday apr-6-2016 17:28:16 bstbid now | add to watch list url779
sb	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	new nike sb : £ 15.00 ( 0 bids ) end date : wednesday apr-6-2016 17:28:16 bstbid now | add to watch list url779
wednesday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	new nike sb : £ 15.00 ( 0 bids ) end date : wednesday apr-6-2016 17:28:16 bstbid now | add to watch list url779
apr-6-2016	PROPN	O	NUM	B-MISC	new nike sb : £ 15.00 ( 0 bids ) end date : wednesday apr-6-2016 17:28:16 bstbid now | add to watch list url779
cns	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	top catholic news * women leaders share their stories at vatican event : vatican city ( cns ) -- in the heart ... url542
#rednose4kids	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using #rednose4kids and @user1905 will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …
@user1905	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using #rednose4kids and @user1905 will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …
#adidas	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	"rt @user1351 : #adidas ultra boost on sale for $ 136 with code "" c6e2y23e "" and vip membership -> url687 url1572 …"
vip	PROPN	O	X	O	"rt @user1351 : #adidas ultra boost on sale for $ 136 with code "" c6e2y23e "" and vip membership -> url687 url1572 …"
@user1595	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1595 fav and follow me for +40 free follows . 🌈
@user2642	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user908 : . @user2642 plates cabrera to make it 3-0 #mets ! url728
#mets	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user908 : . @user2642 plates cabrera to make it 3-0 #mets ! url728
@user369	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user369 bro there ?
@user394	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user394 @user2234 god forbid you upset daddy
@user2234	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user394 @user2234 god forbid you upset daddy
#seo	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	#miguelramose url809 #seo will manually build 10 high pr web 2.0 pbn url1441
pbn	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	#miguelramose url809 #seo will manually build 10 high pr web 2.0 pbn url1441
hongera	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	kenya is indeed a hotbed of champions ! we rock the world hongera kenya7s . made us so proud #karibunimashujaa #kenya7s @user717 @user745
kenya7s	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	kenya is indeed a hotbed of champions ! we rock the world hongera kenya7s . made us so proud #karibunimashujaa #kenya7s @user717 @user745
@user717	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	kenya is indeed a hotbed of champions ! we rock the world hongera kenya7s . made us so proud #karibunimashujaa #kenya7s @user717 @user745
@user745	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	kenya is indeed a hotbed of champions ! we rock the world hongera kenya7s . made us so proud #karibunimashujaa #kenya7s @user717 @user745
terra	PROPN	O	X	O	hello terra , teeshirts and hoodies are named by u ! order now ! : url577 . thank @user1666 url677
@user1666	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	hello terra , teeshirts and hoodies are named by u ! order now ! : url577 . thank @user1666 url677
junior	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	register now for the junior @user136 u8/10/12/14/16/19 - easter 2017 - just £ 290 pp
@user136	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	register now for the junior @user136 u8/10/12/14/16/19 - easter 2017 - just £ 290 pp
u8/10/12/14/16/19	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	register now for the junior @user136 u8/10/12/14/16/19 - easter 2017 - just £ 290 pp
@user57	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user57 request you to share us your booking details for us to look into the issue
@user1409	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2076 : . i apologise for this , but i hope every pro-eu @user1409 member reads it . it 's so important . url1620
gdp	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user994 : quality of life matters more than gdp . our infrastructure is at breaking point inside eu . #bbcqt url1486
@user53	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user53 as do i . i 've always been a fan of honda and acura sports cars . there 's just something about them that i love so much .
may	PROPN	O	AUX	O	dunedin income growth investment tr plc $ dig to go ex-dividend on may 5th url494
@user82	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user82 i 'll braid your hair and make u soup if u want
@user263	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user263 and this is why i 've always hated billy joel . goddammit , billy joel .
@user1534	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1534 d985 5535 08aa 4def
@user2456	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2456 it 's like the world is digitally modified with this layover . it 's hard to explain but super colorful , animated and hyperreal
@user2072	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2072 smh someone from an account as @user417 😂 does n't sound racist at all .
@user417	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2072 smh someone from an account as @user417 😂 does n't sound racist at all .
#truelovethm	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-PER	#win a £ 50 voucher . valid at over 1 k restaurants to enter rt&f with #truelovethm & register url1039 url842
@user1573	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1573 headcanon accepted
@user812	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238
@user1335	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238
@user1790	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238
#cleanupjnu	PROPN	O	VERB	B-ORG	rt @user1635 : #cleanupjnu agree with everything , but right to free speech has limits and the people need to understand that .. url223 …
@user1486	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1535 : so @user1486 were by far the best set of the day , even after the idiots at slamdunk fucked their set up and did nt allow t …
@user1461	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1461 exactly . it does n't add up
@user969	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user969 @user1500 @user2010 @user1175 @user1166 nop sleep is far from my eyes tonight
@user1500	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user969 @user1500 @user2010 @user1175 @user1166 nop sleep is far from my eyes tonight
@user2010	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user969 @user1500 @user2010 @user1175 @user1166 nop sleep is far from my eyes tonight
@user1175	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user969 @user1500 @user2010 @user1175 @user1166 nop sleep is far from my eyes tonight
@user1166	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user969 @user1500 @user2010 @user1175 @user1166 nop sleep is far from my eyes tonight
@user1412	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user468 : 71 years ago today , @user1412 #marines began the battle for iwo jima . url308
#marines	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	rt @user468 : 71 years ago today , @user1412 #marines began the battle for iwo jima . url308
@user1018	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1018 hope you have a good one !! 😊
@user1921	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1880 : @user1921 you already know this us . url450
@user1617	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	success in duckland last night for the @user1617 first eatwith dinner ! thanks to everyone … url290
#abb	PROPN	O	VERB	B-ORG	watch this #abb video : url1439 - ron popper talks about human rights and its importance for abb url793
@user2575	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2575 i just saw this
@user1619	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1907 : @user1619 employers want to pay only for what they need , and they ’re getting comfortable with hiring gig workers , often remo …
@user1458	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	staples now selling recycle - by - mail boxes url922 via @user1458 url1524
@user927	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	. @user927 @user1042 @user341 and jeb does n't , of course ... url1070
@user1042	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	. @user927 @user1042 @user341 and jeb does n't , of course ... url1070
@user341	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	. @user927 @user1042 @user341 and jeb does n't , of course ... url1070
owari	PROPN	O	SPACE	B-ORG	subete no owari
@user2127	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2127 have fun kiddo
@user2434	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	. @user2434 really likes socks , i 've heard ! ;3 url1292
@user2662	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2662 because you thought i was a scumbag and followed me to roast my soul
#ralphlauren	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	classy range of #men #footwear for him featuring #ralphlauren #tods #originalpenguin & more ! url251 url1503
#tods	PROPN	O	ADP	O	classy range of #men #footwear for him featuring #ralphlauren #tods #originalpenguin & more ! url251 url1503
#originalpenguin	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	classy range of #men #footwear for him featuring #ralphlauren #tods #originalpenguin & more ! url251 url1503
ca	PROPN	O	AUX	O	9917 s mission blvd , jurupa valley , ca 92509 sold on 6/17/16 listed for $ 385,000 sold for … url1235
modest	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	rt @user1933 : modest literally trapped zayn holy
@user875	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user875 need to work hard on your content , just had a look at city 's twitter and it 's way more interesting ..
@user306	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user306 of course !!! lol
subhan	PROPN	O	X	O	rt @user1126 : subhan ' allah . the only cloud in the whole sky is blocking the sun & protecting those who are worshipping . url567 …
allah	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1126 : subhan ' allah . the only cloud in the whole sky is blocking the sun & protecting those who are worshipping . url567 …
lpg	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user2285 : massive mission to be launched to provide lpg connections to bpl households : fm
@user1746	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1746 what say you home ? 😘❤️
k-5	PROPN	O	X	O	2015 - 2016 donald publishing award winners k-5 . #authorstea @user373 @user1834 url949
@user985	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user405 : @user985 @user142 also on @user1287 #cantbeintwoplacesatonce #poororganisation url1220
@user142	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user405 : @user985 @user142 also on @user1287 #cantbeintwoplacesatonce #poororganisation url1220
@user1287	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user405 : @user985 @user142 also on @user1287 #cantbeintwoplacesatonce #poororganisation url1220
#rhony	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user88 : really good #rhony tonight .
#minioncarpet	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-ORG	rt @user1116 : #win ( 20 m2 ) 5 m x 4 m #minioncarpet from @user1116 #rt & #follow #competition #giveaway url843 ht …
@user1116	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1116 : #win ( 20 m2 ) 5 m x 4 m #minioncarpet from @user1116 #rt & #follow #competition #giveaway url843 ht …
ig	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1051 : podenco lounging with a ball is our definition of #weekendgoals . ( ig kurti_podenco ) url1252
@user530	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user1960 : msg @user530 ji please bless to serve humanity with full zeal !! 🙏☺ #savehumanitysaysmsg need blessings 24 * 7 ! ☺ url219 …
ji	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1960 : msg @user530 ji please bless to serve humanity with full zeal !! 🙏☺ #savehumanitysaysmsg need blessings 24 * 7 ! ☺ url219 …
pokémon	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	you 'd be a grass - type pokémon ! folks admire your natural grace and spirit . your ideal day is to bask in the warmth of the sun . what the fuck
@user968	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user577 : self - harm such an important topic not spoken enough ! pls read @user968 piece ♥ #selfharmawarenessday url1504 …
@user1490	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	gigi hadid and zayn malik feature in us vogue magazine for couple 's first photoshoot : url1123 via @user1490
@user2210	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2210 love them all but i have to say lone survivor is my favorite
@user195	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user195 snoopy van gough 😊
#trumptrain	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	donald trump #trumptrain 2016 large black custom decal intlship #republican #2a #sgp #optrump url1006
custom	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	donald trump #trumptrain 2016 large black custom decal intlship #republican #2a #sgp #optrump url1006
decal	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	donald trump #trumptrain 2016 large black custom decal intlship #republican #2a #sgp #optrump url1006
v180	PROPN	O	ADP	B-MISC	"great deals >> url265 new eclipse v180 1.8 "" lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262"
lcd	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	"great deals >> url265 new eclipse v180 1.8 "" lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262"
usb	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	"great deals >> url265 new eclipse v180 1.8 "" lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262"
mp3	PROPN	O	X	O	"great deals >> url265 new eclipse v180 1.8 "" lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262"
@user2591	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user2478 : @user2591 be tolerant to criticism young man , you also will be buddhe ek din like me
buddhe	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	rt @user2478 : @user2591 be tolerant to criticism young man , you also will be buddhe ek din like me
ek	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2478 : @user2591 be tolerant to criticism young man , you also will be buddhe ek din like me
din	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user2478 : @user2591 be tolerant to criticism young man , you also will be buddhe ek din like me
#mtvhottest	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	212 xo #mtvhottest beyonce coldplay meghan trainor
@user1087	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1087 i hope you like our very first inclusion campaign ! l
@user2326	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2326 literally what is he talking about someone come get h
@user520	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user520 always a pleasure . have a great weekend xx
@user936	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user946 : @user936 @user937 did someone say pony !? 😮😄😃😎
@user937	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user946 : @user936 @user937 did someone say pony !? 😮😄😃😎
#freebiefriday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user1953 : there 's still time to enter our #freebiefriday to win an amazon voucher . just keep following and retweeting ! #fridayfeeling
@user1490	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	diggy - 4 letter word [ official video ] url440 via @user1490
model	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user725 : have you seen this ? tesla model s drives sleeping owner through traffic : a video of a napping driver behind t ... url225 …
s	PROPN	O	VERB	O	rt @user725 : have you seen this ? tesla model s drives sleeping owner through traffic : a video of a napping driver behind t ... url225 …
#rncincle	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user1328 : americans prefer war heroes , even if they were captured : trump #rncincle speech drew lower ratings than mccain ' 08 url218 …
@user742	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user742 appreciate it fam !
@user958	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user958 before the shittery starts about him playing for villa . so what ? saw him play a fair bit for nice , he 's a tidy player and an upgrade
duramax	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	rt @user2592 : looking for a 6.6l duramax . will trade my camry . #allisonforlife
camry	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2592 : looking for a 6.6l duramax . will trade my camry . #allisonforlife
@user759	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !
@user2188	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !
@user2003	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !
@user694	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !
@user1670	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !
#hillaryclinton	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-PER	mjanemann : url523 #fbimwithher #emailgate more rules that #hillaryclinton ... url481
@user2604	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	way to stoked for this ! s/o to @user2604 for this awesome flyer ! #rad #radmusic #radaf … url486
@user680	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user680 @user1421 @user354 @user358 @user1519 forgot me but ily big papi
@user1421	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user680 @user1421 @user354 @user358 @user1519 forgot me but ily big papi
@user354	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user680 @user1421 @user354 @user358 @user1519 forgot me but ily big papi
@user358	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user680 @user1421 @user354 @user358 @user1519 forgot me but ily big papi
@user1519	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user680 @user1421 @user354 @user358 @user1519 forgot me but ily big papi
@user1669	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1669 wow . that 's pretty intense !
@user1728	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user261 : @user1728 @user1586 @user2199 happy #aldub42ndweeksary : 42 = 24 ! the numbers 2 and 4 ❤️😊
@user1586	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user261 : @user1728 @user1586 @user2199 happy #aldub42ndweeksary : 42 = 24 ! the numbers 2 and 4 ❤️😊
@user2199	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user261 : @user1728 @user1586 @user2199 happy #aldub42ndweeksary : 42 = 24 ! the numbers 2 and 4 ❤️😊
@user255	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user255 thanks so much :)
@user2612	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2612 i think you 're doing pretty well and do n't really need a plan b. ;-)
@user2143	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2143 you cant run from the truth vivi !! you are a furry !!
lb	PROPN	O	X	O	eagles round out draft with lb walker url1546
@user1945	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1945 thnk u 💜💜
@user1700	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1700 lol thanks
@user386	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user386 i fav your tweets and talk to you all the time 😭😭 why you got to treat me like this
@user1002	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1002 who is they
@user1613	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user2357	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user2452	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user2588	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user2236	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user377	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user1139	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user1298	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user2419	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1613 @user2357 @user2452 @user2588 @user2236 @user377 @user1139 @user1298 @user2419 thanks
@user1690	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1690 yeah everythings fine now !! it was taken care of , i m hoping the problem wo nt come back tho but u kno ..... ^_____t
@user589	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user589 my pleasure , as always ! thanks for the retweet ! 💗
#mancandymonday	PROPN	O	NOUN	B-MISC	rt @user1918 : #omarlives !! #longmireonnetflix #longmire happy #mancandymonday url1554
@user2050	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	rt @user24 : i want to win @user2050 dm pack url1445
eurusd	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-ORG	order closed at p/l of $ 0.93 . ticket 123546591 buy 0.01 lots eurusd - url1085
@user2185	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user2185 maybe do sprints . a great way to increase calorie burn .
#swish	PROPN	O	ADJ	O	rt @user2495 : #swish will be signing at sunday 's game 12 - 12:20 pm ( tix required ) . gates - 12 pm , 1st pitch - 1:05 pm #gorailriders url222 …
sunday	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user2495 : #swish will be signing at sunday 's game 12 - 12:20 pm ( tix required ) . gates - 12 pm , 1st pitch - 1:05 pm #gorailriders url222 …
#twitter	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	rt @user809 : here are 5 ways for you to start using #twitter to market your #business : url1320 url1262
@user1041	PROPN	O	User: No change	B-PER	@user1041 happy birthday !
#bb18	PROPN	O	X	B-ORG	rt @user165 : delay update : #bb18 will air at 8:40 / 7:40 c !
usb	PROPN	O	PROPN	B-MISC	huge daily deals > url1224 #6180 #1954 50 wholesale lot of frisby usb 2.0 computer pc laptop noteb … url848
