651	@user1790	14	14	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on <[@user1790]> at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
298	@user2652	17	17	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user411 laughing matter = me being serious . just watch . be encouraged !! url172 via @user2652	rt @user411 laughing matter = me being serious . just watch . be encouraged !! url172 via <[@user2652]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
650	@user1335	6	6	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	win tix to see @user812 at <[@user1335]> on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
344	@user1295	9	9	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rain rain go away <-- our song is on @user1295 i kid you not 107.5	rain rain go away <-- our song is on <[@user1295]> i kid you not 107.5	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
649	@user812	4	4	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	win tix to see @user812 at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	win tix to see <[@user812]> at @user1335 on 8/12 . tune in today on @user1790 at 6 p pt to win url632 url1238	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
635	@user136	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	register now for the junior @user136 u8/10/12/14/16/19 - easter 2017 - just £ 290 pp	register now for the junior <[@user136]> u8/10/12/14/16/19 - easter 2017 - just £ 290 pp	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
353	@user2350	11	11	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	the onion weighs in on the wisconsin senate race url99 via @user2350	the onion weighs in on the wisconsin senate race url99 via <[@user2350]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
619	@user1905	9	9	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using #rednose4kids and @user1905 will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using #rednose4kids and <[@user1905]> will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
614	@user2582	9	9	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	i just earned the ' newbie ' badge on @user2582 ! url716	i just earned the ' newbie ' badge on <[@user2582]> ! url716	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
589	@user2630	14	14	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	want a chance to win some prizes from @user1440 ? just head over to @user2630 and enter ! url856	want a chance to win some prizes from @user1440 ? just head over to <[@user2630]> and enter ! url856	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
368	@user2615	8	8	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	url43 making it easy to put up a @user2615 , @user2070 in the cloud #aws	url43 making it easy to put up a <[@user2615]> , @user2070 in the cloud #aws	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		put what in the cloud?
660	@user1412	8	8	['PROPN']	['NUM']	['NUM']	['O']	[]	rt @user468 : 71 years ago today , @user1412 #marines began the battle for iwo jima . url308	rt @user468 : 71 years ago today , <[@user1412]> #marines began the battle for iwo jima . url308	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
369	@user2070	10	10	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	url43 making it easy to put up a @user2615 , @user2070 in the cloud #aws	url43 making it easy to put up a @user2615 , <[@user2070]> in the cloud #aws	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		put what in the cloud?
588	@user1440	8	8	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	want a chance to win some prizes from @user1440 ? just head over to @user2630 and enter ! url856	want a chance to win some prizes from <[@user1440]> ? just head over to @user2630 and enter ! url856	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
573	@user2227	13	13	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	i saw this early & thought it was pretty fun to watch ! @user2227 was great ! are you going to see it ? 🎬🎥 url370	i saw this early & thought it was pretty fun to watch ! <[@user2227]> was great ! are you going to see it ? 🎬🎥 url370	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
568	@user121	21	21	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	istanbul airport attack : 23 turks , at least 10 foreign nationals killed , officials say , as ... url880 via @user121	istanbul airport attack : 23 turks , at least 10 foreign nationals killed , officials say , as ... url880 via <[@user121]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
542	@user913	18	18	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user637 : underground clinics in turkey treating syria 's wounded jihadist terrorists to fight on url539 via @user913 …	rt @user637 : underground clinics in turkey treating syria 's wounded jihadist terrorists to fight on url539 via <[@user913]> …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
525	@user986	4	4	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	new lara vapnyer in @user986 this week ! :d this will be my special treat after i am finished teaching for the day . hearts	new lara vapnyer in <[@user986]> this week ! :d this will be my special treat after i am finished teaching for the day . hearts	B-PER	B-LOC	B-PER		
397	@user388	10	10	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	the @user963 draft is thursday makes me want to play @user388 anyone want to get down ?? #youdontwantitwithme !	the @user963 draft is thursday makes me want to play <[@user388]> anyone want to get down ?? #youdontwantitwithme !	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		
513	@user1059	19	19	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user576 : whoo ! on march 16th i 'll be having a charity stream on twitch to benefit @user1059 !! mark your calendars ! url221 …	rt @user576 : whoo ! on march 16th i 'll be having a charity stream on twitch to benefit <[@user1059]> !! mark your calendars ! url221 …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
509	uk	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	['PERSON']	i totally agree ban islam uk url512	i totally agree ban islam <[uk]> url512	B-PER	B-LOC	B-MISC	B-LOC	
403	@user1934	3	3	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	retweeted globalpublishing ( @user1934 ) : atmosphere permits light and heat to reach earth at levels ... url534	retweeted globalpublishing ( <[@user1934]> ) : atmosphere permits light and heat to reach earth at levels ... url534	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
498	@user1885	15	15	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	@user1622 @user218 will you please help pass the message about my aunties dying wish on @user1885 it would mean so much to me and her 💖	@user1622 @user218 will you please help pass the message about my aunties dying wish on <[@user1885]> it would mean so much to me and her 💖	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
494	@user2155	6	6	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user2154 : " the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today " #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …	rt @user2154 : " the #studentexperience <[@user2155]> has made me who i am today " #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		prob talking about a school
372	@user375	1	1	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	if @user375 do nt make some hoodies soon ... imma beat em !	if <[@user375]> do nt make some hoodies soon ... imma beat em !	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		could be org/per/etc.
456	@user2066	9	9	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	oh yeah ! spanked em ! way to go @user2066 #nascar 🏁 #ford	oh yeah ! spanked em ! way to go <[@user2066]> #nascar 🏁 #ford	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
3	@user1598	1	1	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	@user1598 : super junior ’s siwon transforms into ‘ captain choi ’ for “ poseidon ” url139	<[@user1598]> : super junior ’s siwon transforms into ‘ captain choi ’ for “ poseidon ” url139	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
887	@user268	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user978 : #nvthots vs. @user268 in the semifinals ! battle of the na powerhouses . watch : url1106 #ourfight url221 …	rt @user978 : #nvthots vs. <[@user268]> in the semifinals ! battle of the na powerhouses . watch : url1106 #ourfight url221 …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		could be person
113	@user497	2	2	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	@user1034 follow @user497 & win ca$h playing your favorite video games ! #gamersaloon	@user1034 follow <[@user497]> & win ca$h playing your favorite video games ! #gamersaloon	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
130	@user398	12	12	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	@user1309 in bham i & teamel_al will be in full effect 4 @user398 10/30/10 !	@user1309 in bham i & teamel_al will be in full effect 4 <[@user398]> 10/30/10 !	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		event
859	@user2581	5	5	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	i 'm using whatsapp+ by @user2581 for ios to add new features to whatsapp ! url734	i 'm using whatsapp+ by <[@user2581]> for ios to add new features to whatsapp ! url734	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
668	@user1458	11	11	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	staples now selling recycle - by - mail boxes url922 via @user1458 url1524	staples now selling recycle - by - mail boxes url922 via <[@user1458]> url1524	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
817	@user477	4	4	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	listening now @user1603 437 @user477 yesterday episode !! gooooo !!! #trancefamily #fsoe437	listening now @user1603 437 <[@user477]> yesterday episode !! gooooo !!! #trancefamily #fsoe437	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		based on context, person first show later
259	@user1035	19	19	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	david mitchell 's immersive reading room , the " ultimate environment " to enjoy thousand autumns : url75 /via @user1035	david mitchell 's immersive reading room , the " ultimate environment " to enjoy thousand autumns : url75 /via <[@user1035]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
772	@user1739	6	6	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	i liked a @user1490 video from @user1739 url1400 molten aluminum vs bullets	i liked a @user1490 video from <[@user1739]> url1400 molten aluminum vs bullets	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
756	@user2050	7	7	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user24 : i want to win @user2050 dm pack url1445	rt @user24 : i want to win <[@user2050]> dm pack url1445	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER		product
720	@user759	0	0	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	@user759 @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !	<[@user759]> @user2188 @user2003 @user694 @user1670 shhh , do n't tell her !	B-PER	B-PER	O		
275	@user1490	3	3	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	i uploaded a @user1490 video url116 paris.flv	i uploaded a <[@user1490]> video url116 paris.flv	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
714	@user1490	11	11	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	diggy - 4 letter word [ official video ] url440 via @user1490	diggy - 4 letter word [ official video ] url440 via <[@user1490]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
692	@user1116	15	15	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user1116 : #win ( 20 m2 ) 5 m x 4 m #minioncarpet from @user1116 #rt & #follow #competition #giveaway url843 ht …	rt @user1116 : #win ( 20 m2 ) 5 m x 4 m #minioncarpet from <[@user1116]> #rt & #follow #competition #giveaway url843 ht …	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
804	@user2361	20	20	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	#bbcdp ukip ’s only councillor in wales resigns in epic letter slamming farage ’s “ political cronyism ” url794 via @user2361	#bbcdp ukip ’s only councillor in wales resigns in epic letter slamming farage ’s “ political cronyism ” url794 via <[@user2361]>	B-PER	B-ORG	B-PER		
449	@user1923	0	0	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	@user1923 did n't eat enough did i 🙄	<[@user1923]> did n't eat enough did i 🙄	B-PER	B-PER			
919	#cheo’s	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN', 'PART']	['PROPN', 'PART']	['O']	['ORG']	#volunteers are key members of #cheo’s one team – helping kids and families be their healthiest #nvw2016 url1387	#volunteers are key members of <[#cheo’s]> one team – helping kids and families be their healthiest #nvw2016 url1387	B-ORG	B-ORG	B-PER	B-ORG	
358	#jeopardy	2	2	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	['ORG']	weird , #jeopardy is alluding to the charlie the unicorn video in their clue titles ! shun the non-believer !	weird , <[#jeopardy]> is alluding to the charlie the unicorn video in their clue titles ! shun the non-believer !	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	
406	#24audiolaunch	9	9	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	['FAC']	rt @user2020 : to all suriya fans coming to #24audiolaunch on monday - no photos or videos allowed inside the venue .	rt @user2020 : to all suriya fans coming to <[#24audiolaunch]> on monday - no photos or videos allowed inside the venue .	B-LOC	B-MISC	B-LOC	B-MISC	
252	suv	14	14	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	calgary 1980 pontiac trans am t tops $ 4,900.00 over 175 cars trucks and suv 's 90 day warrenty ... url175	calgary 1980 pontiac trans am t tops $ 4,900.00 over 175 cars trucks and <[suv]> 's 90 day warrenty ... url175	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
359	pimpin	1	1	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	whaddup pimpin ken . ha !	whaddup <[pimpin]> ken . ha !	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
617	cns	16	16	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	top catholic news * women leaders share their stories at vatican event : vatican city ( cns ) -- in the heart ... url542	top catholic news * women leaders share their stories at vatican event : vatican city ( <[cns]> ) -- in the heart ... url542	B-MISC	B-LOC	B-MISC	B-ORG	??? LW: Catholic News Service
842	woodseaves	6	6	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	['PRODUCT']	offer : laptop case new ( woodseaves ) url786	offer : laptop case new ( <[woodseaves]> ) url786	B-MISC	B-LOC	B-MISC	B-LOC	??? LW: Woodseaves, England
145	jesus	2	2	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	@user1475 @user732 jesus are you two still at it ? lolx	@user1475 @user732 <[jesus]> are you two still at it ? lolx	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
352	ex	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	the modern vacation : with ex ’s and new partners url150	the modern vacation : with <[ex]> ’s and new partners url150	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
200	tims	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	@user2252 can we go to tims please and tonkkss	@user2252 can we go to <[tims]> please and tonkkss	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	restuarant location
806	#demsinphilly	11	11	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user2566 : the dnc is now collection #berniesanders signs inside #demsinphilly trying to silence protesters #dncleak #dncinphl url218 …	rt @user2566 : the dnc is now collection #berniesanders signs inside <[#demsinphilly]> trying to silence protesters #dncleak #dncinphl url218 …	B-MISC	O	B-LOC	O	
225	#virgin	2	2	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	@user2502 glad #virgin is keeping you happy !	@user2502 glad <[#virgin]> is keeping you happy !	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	
294	loblaws	1	1	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	oh loblaws you kill me , 4 - 8	oh <[loblaws]> you kill me , 4 - 8	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
679	modest	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1933 : modest literally trapped zayn holy	rt @user1933 : <[modest]> literally trapped zayn holy	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-PER	O	could be a band, or a person
236	@user1463	9	9	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	['WORK_OF_ART']	andrew - check out more tracks from the upcoming @user1463 albums : url95 & url100 :) .	andrew - check out more tracks from the upcoming <[@user1463]> albums : url95 & url100 :) .	B-MISC	B-MISC	B-PER		could be band, labeled as work of art for now
276	#bet	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	idk what this movie on #bet is but i 've seen it before and it s hilarious !	idk what this movie on <[#bet]> is but i 've seen it before and it s hilarious !	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-MISC	
270	jasmine	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	hungryyyyy ( @ jasmine 26 ) url6	hungryyyyy ( @ <[jasmine]> 26 ) url6	B-MISC	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER	
739	lb	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	eagles round out draft with lb walker url1546	eagles round out draft with <[lb]> walker url1546	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
266	uv	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	haha . my producer said uv vodka is a bad situation waitin to happen , i said #fuuuuuuucccit	haha . my producer said <[uv]> vodka is a bad situation waitin to happen , i said #fuuuuuuucccit	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-MISC	??? LW: Brand of Vodka
362	#snowto	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	where 's this #snowto at ? let 's see what you 've got #toronto	where 's this <[#snowto]> at ? let 's see what you 've got #toronto	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	B-MISC	??? LW: SnowTO (Snow Toronto) - just a hashtag from the City of Toronto
12	jordan	13	13	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	#jordanheels are very useful in a fight cause a hoodrat will put a jordan stamp n hole in ur dome lls	#jordanheels are very useful in a fight cause a hoodrat will put a <[jordan]> stamp n hole in ur dome lls	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	
886	#nvthots	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user978 : #nvthots vs. @user268 in the semifinals ! battle of the na powerhouses . watch : url1106 #ourfight url221 …	rt @user978 : <[#nvthots]> vs. @user268 in the semifinals ! battle of the na powerhouses . watch : url1106 #ourfight url221 …	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	could be person
5	gospel	12	12	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	do n't move on from the gospel , move into the gospel !  todd friel	do n't move on from the gospel , move into the <[gospel]> !  todd friel	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
418	#mpoints	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	i 'm earning #mpoints with #askdaball ! url1271 #app	i 'm earning <[#mpoints]> with #askdaball ! url1271 #app	B-MISC	B-MISC	O	O	
391	grill	4	4	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	free char - broil grill ( hilliard ) url1473	free char - broil <[grill]> ( hilliard ) url1473	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
913	ft	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1701 : ft island - i hope ( 2009 ) url1510	rt @user1701 : <[ft]> island - i hope ( 2009 ) url1510	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
13	dj	1	1	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	#np dj got us - falling in love ag - u$her ft. pitbull	#np <[dj]> got us - falling in love ag - u$her ft. pitbull	B-MISC	O	B-PER	O	
419	#askdaball	5	5	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	i 'm earning #mpoints with #askdaball ! url1271 #app	i 'm earning #mpoints with <[#askdaball]> ! url1271 #app	B-MISC	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	
533	keen	19	19	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	url824 retweeted i 'm in the arndale centre i have 8 hours to wait for the signing talk about keen url690	url824 retweeted i 'm in the arndale centre i have 8 hours to wait for the signing talk about <[keen]> url690	B-MISC	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	??? LW: Not sure, but context suggests that it is a work of art
550	#sdcc2016	6	6	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user777 : friday night at #sdcc2016 with sis , @user1679 covered in magic ! #onceuponatime #evilregalsdcc ❤️🦄💚 url1178	rt @user777 : friday night at <[#sdcc2016]> with sis , @user1679 covered in magic ! #onceuponatime #evilregalsdcc ❤️🦄💚 url1178	B-MISC	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	
4	gospel	7	7	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	do n't move on from the gospel , move into the gospel !  todd friel	do n't move on from the <[gospel]> , move into the gospel !  todd friel	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
909	#lindaikeji	0	0	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	#lindaikeji post - wendy williams thinks beyonce and jay z paid rachel roy for the cheating … url229 url1196	<[#lindaikeji]> post - wendy williams thinks beyonce and jay z paid rachel roy for the cheating … url229 url1196	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-PER	B-PER	??? LW: Nigerian blogger
389	svt	3	3	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1855 : svt when people keep voting for sweden url1528	rt @user1855 : <[svt]> when people keep voting for sweden url1528	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
481	mrs	8	8	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['PROPN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1346 : when your mate who 's mrs rarely lets him out makes it to the pub url1013	rt @user1346 : when your mate who 's <[mrs]> rarely lets him out makes it to the pub url1013	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	O	
796	#superjunior	6	6	['PROPN']	['ADJ']	['ADJ']	['O']	[]	my teen choice for #choicemusicgroupmale is #superjunior my #teenchoice nominee for #choicefandom is #elf 289	my teen choice for #choicemusicgroupmale is <[#superjunior]> my #teenchoice nominee for #choicefandom is #elf 289	O	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-MISC	
249	#napflow	6	6	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	bbm yawn face * man that #napflow felt so refreshing .	bbm yawn face * man that <[#napflow]> felt so refreshing .	O	B-MISC	O	O	LW: might just refer to a nap
140	title	19	19	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	@user1448 does n't change anything if it 's a " best seller . " ie @user695 and the wwe title . most businesses reinvest their profits into new things	@user1448 does n't change anything if it 's a " best seller . " ie @user695 and the wwe <[title]> . most businesses reinvest their profits into new things	O	O	B-MISC	O	
797	#teenchoice	8	8	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	my teen choice for #choicemusicgroupmale is #superjunior my #teenchoice nominee for #choicefandom is #elf 289	my teen choice for #choicemusicgroupmale is #superjunior my <[#teenchoice]> nominee for #choicefandom is #elf 289	O	O	B-MISC	B-MISC	???? LW: Award name
9	#lebronshould	0	0	['PROPN']	['PRON']	['PRON']	['O']	[]	#lebronshould know his only championship is ' slam dunk ' . @user2004	<[#lebronshould]> know his only championship is ' slam dunk ' . @user2004	O	B-PER	B-MISC	B-PER	
235	flutes	2	2	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	ahh . flutes sound really bad with cheap mics . writing a song now , just need chords and i 'll be good . bye :d	ahh . <[flutes]> sound really bad with cheap mics . writing a song now , just need chords and i 'll be good . bye :d	O	O	B-MISC	O	
857	#choiceanteencipatedmovieactress	7	7	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user2172 : my #teenchoice vote for #choiceanteencipatedmovieactress is @user92 url1173	rt @user2172 : my #teenchoice vote for <[#choiceanteencipatedmovieactress]> is @user92 url1173	O	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	AWARD Name
878	ai	20	20	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user977 : an emotional journey from working at a call - centre , to cern and award - winning ai research url1182 url221 …	rt @user977 : an emotional journey from working at a call - centre , to cern and award - winning <[ai]> research url1182 url221 …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
867	#blockchain	19	19	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user452 : santander uk introduces a mobile payment app for its staff to transfer money built on the #blockchain url1416	rt @user452 : santander uk introduces a mobile payment app for its staff to transfer money built on the <[#blockchain]> url1416	O	O	B-MISC	O	
838	anti-apartheid	2	2	['PROPN']	['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ']	['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ']	['O']	[]	parole for anti-apartheid hero ’s killer ? victim ’s family says ‘ no ! ’ : ( url258 ) — the wife of a … url1121	parole for <[anti-apartheid]> hero ’s killer ? victim ’s family says ‘ no ! ’ : ( url258 ) — the wife of a … url1121	O	O	B-MISC	O	can be misc as well?
15	d	10	10	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	3-0 !! phew !!! good no td !!! go job d !!! #birdgang	3-0 !! phew !!! good no td !!! go job <[d]> !!! #birdgang	O	B-PER	O	O	
48	#etp	5	5	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning #etp fam	@user473 @user948 @user1227 , morning <[#etp]> fam	O	B-ORG	O	B-ORG	
757	eurusd	13	13	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	order closed at p/l of $ 0.93 . ticket 123546591 buy 0.01 lots eurusd - url1085	order closed at p/l of $ 0.93 . ticket 123546591 buy 0.01 lots <[eurusd]> - url1085	O	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	
385	g310	0	0	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	g310 . not bad !! ( pic via fb ) url1021	<[g310]> . not bad !! ( pic via fb ) url1021	O	B-MISC	O	O	
559	rs.	14	14	['PROPN']	['NOUN', 'NOUN']	['NOUN', 'NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1990 : oneplus 3 to come to india 15th june will start at rs. 23999 url951 #oneplus #india #oneplus3	rt @user1990 : oneplus 3 to come to india 15th june will start at <[rs.]> 23999 url951 #oneplus #india #oneplus3	O	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	
398	#teenchoice	1	1	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	my #teenchoice for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016	my <[#teenchoice]> for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016	O	O	B-MISC	O	
399	#choicemusicgroup	3	3	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	my #teenchoice for #choicemusicgroup is @user21 ! 31.05.2016	my #teenchoice for <[#choicemusicgroup]> is @user21 ! 31.05.2016	O	B-MISC	B-ORG	B-MISC	???
495	#uniexperience	15	15	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user2154 : " the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today " #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …	rt @user2154 : " the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today " <[#uniexperience]> video : url805 url220 …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
493	#studentexperience	5	5	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user2154 : " the #studentexperience @user2155 has made me who i am today " #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …	rt @user2154 : " the <[#studentexperience]> @user2155 has made me who i am today " #uniexperience video : url805 url220 …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
485	cnblue	4	4	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user966 : 20160319 cnblue #cometogetherinchongqing url767 url1452	rt @user966 : 20160319 <[cnblue]> #cometogetherinchongqing url767 url1452	O	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-ORG	band
470	bright	9	9	['PROPN']	['ADJ']	['ADJ']	['O']	[]	rt @user2330 : save the best for you shine bright glen	rt @user2330 : save the best for you shine <[bright]> glen	O	O	B-MISC	O	
429	cavsin6	9	9	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! cavsin6 @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458	rt @user1350 : y'all heard it here first ! <[cavsin6]> @user225 @user1211 @user1348 @user458	O	B-PER	B-MISC	B-ORG	??? LW: Cleveland Cavaliers
375	wessss	0	0	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	wessss keep metal hjahah \m/ rt @user47 : metal	<[wessss]> keep metal hjahah \m/ rt @user47 : metal	O	B-PER	O	B-PER	
603	#educatorsplaybook	3	3	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1048 : #educatorsplaybook : @user379 offers advice for high school athletes choosing colleges url572 url222 …	rt @user1048 : <[#educatorsplaybook]> : @user379 offers advice for high school athletes choosing colleges url572 url222 …	O	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	brand
611	caravan	20	20	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this caravan ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …	rt @user615 : @user1581 this unstoppable carvan vl go far ! satan & his disciples has not much power2stop this <[caravan]> ! #200daysmsg2 s a bash …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
702	v180	6	6	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	great deals >> url265 new eclipse v180 1.8 " lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262	great deals >> url265 new eclipse <[v180]> 1.8 " lcd 8 gb usb 2.0 digital music / video mp3 player url262	O	B-MISC	O	O	referring to a product
278	giving	3	3	['PROPN']	['VERB']	['VERB']	['O']	[]	is today thanks giving ? :l	is today thanks <[giving]> ? :l	O	B-MISC	O	O	
279	jihad	1	1	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	islamic jihad militant killed near gaza border url36	islamic <[jihad]> militant killed near gaza border url36	O	B-ORG	B-MISC	O	
690	#rhony	5	5	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user88 : really good #rhony tonight .	rt @user88 : really good <[#rhony]> tonight .	O	B-MISC	O	B-MISC	real housewives of nyc show
288	getto	5	5	['PROPN']	['X']	['X']	['O']	[]	microwaved grilled cheese / the getto grilled cheese sandwhich / they 're made with real cheese #haiku #mooku	microwaved grilled cheese / the <[getto]> grilled cheese sandwhich / they 're made with real cheese #haiku #mooku	O	O	B-MISC	O	
320	tonite	8	8	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1069 where is punk ass , @user1197 tonite !!! < honestly who cares ?? :-p	rt @user1069 where is punk ass , @user1197 <[tonite]> !!! < honestly who cares ?? :-p	O	B-MISC	O	O	
345	id	7	7	['PROPN']	['NOUN', 'NOUN']	['NOUN', 'NOUN']	['O']	[]	ruling strikes down part of arizona voter id law - yahoo! news url70	ruling strikes down part of arizona voter <[id]> law - yahoo! news url70	O	O	B-MISC	O	
647	#truelovethm	16	16	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	#win a £ 50 voucher . valid at over 1 k restaurants to enter rt&f with #truelovethm & register url1039 url842	#win a £ 50 voucher . valid at over 1 k restaurants to enter rt&f with <[#truelovethm]> & register url1039 url842	O	O	B-MISC	O	
638	gdp	9	9	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user994 : quality of life matters more than gdp . our infrastructure is at breaking point inside eu . #bbcqt url1486	rt @user994 : quality of life matters more than <[gdp]> . our infrastructure is at breaking point inside eu . #bbcqt url1486	O	O	B-MISC	O	
346	live	1	1	['PROPN']	['ADV']	['ADV']	['O']	[]	showoffradio live !!!	showoffradio <[live]> !!!	O	O	B-MISC	O	
628	#seo	2	2	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	#miguelramose url809 #seo will manually build 10 high pr web 2.0 pbn url1441	#miguelramose url809 <[#seo]> will manually build 10 high pr web 2.0 pbn url1441	O	O	B-MISC	O	
624	#mets	11	11	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user908 : . @user2642 plates cabrera to make it 3-0 #mets ! url728	rt @user908 : . @user2642 plates cabrera to make it 3-0 <[#mets]> ! url728	O	B-ORG	B-MISC	B-MISC	
621	vip	17	17	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1351 : #adidas ultra boost on sale for $ 136 with code " c6e2y23e " and vip membership -> url687 url1572 …	rt @user1351 : #adidas ultra boost on sale for $ 136 with code " c6e2y23e " and <[vip]> membership -> url687 url1572 …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
618	#rednose4kids	7	7	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using #rednose4kids and @user1905 will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …	rt @user1111 : tweet or rt using <[#rednose4kids]> and @user1905 will donate $ 10 to end child poverty . #rednoseday url1607 …	O	O	B-MISC	O	
764	usb	12	12	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	huge daily deals > url1224 #6180 #1954 50 wholesale lot of frisby usb 2.0 computer pc laptop noteb … url848	huge daily deals > url1224 #6180 #1954 50 wholesale lot of frisby <[usb]> 2.0 computer pc laptop noteb … url848	O	O	B-MISC	O	
529	po	10	10	['PROPN']	['NOUN']	['NOUN']	['O']	[]	rt @user2298 : uhm funny po ako 😹 thank you po ! #stbratsexhibit url655	rt @user2298 : uhm funny po ako 😹 thank you <[po]> ! #stbratsexhibit url655	O	O	B-MISC	O	phrase